The Aware Zhao said he first visited there
アウェア・趙は初めてそこを訪れたと語った
Academia Sinica's August Knowledge Feast Lecture Begins
中央研究院の8月の知識の饗宴講義が始まります
We ask Vice President Chen Jianren to host for us
陳建仁副総統に司会をお願いします。
Our protagonist today is Academician Zhang Meihui
今日の主役は学者の張美輝です
And academician Zhang Meihui
そして学者の張美輝
Mr. Tintin is also named
サーはディンディンとも呼ばれます
Lin Zhiming, Dean Lin of this Huotai Hospital
林志明、この火台病院の林院長
we welcome him too
私たちも彼を歓迎します
good
良い
And then gentlemen and ladies
そして紳士淑女の皆様
And my classmates, my friends
そして私のクラスメート、私の友達
Goodnight everybody
おやすみ皆さん
Thank you all for participating in today's feast of knowledge
本日の知の饗宴にご参加いただきました皆様、誠にありがとうございました
What about this event today?
今日のこのイベントはどうでしょうか？
I hosted the most satisfying time for everyone
皆様にとって最高に充実した時間を演出させていただきました
Thank you all for coming here
ここに来てくれてありがとう
We have two hundred people registered
200人が登録しています
When I host a night, there are probably 150 to 160 people.
私が夜を主催すると、おそらく150人から160人が集まります。
So today is Professor Zhang Meihui really has a lot of charm
さて、今日は張美輝先生は本当に魅力がたくさんあります
Professor Zhang Meihui is now a special chair professor of the small department of the National Taiwan University School of Medicine
張美輝教授は現在、国立台湾大学医学部の小学部の特別主任教授となっています。
He is also an academician of our Academia Sinica
彼は中央研究院の学者でもあります。
There are not many women among academicians of Academia Sinica
中央研究院の学者には女性が少ない
Especially life sciences are not many
特にライフサイエンス分野では、
Everyone in the medical field is more familiar with
医療関係者なら誰でもよく知っている
Academician Peng Wang Jiakang
学者彭王嘉康
That is Academician Zhang Meihui
それは学者の張美輝です
Therefore, academician Zhang Meihui and Peng Wangjia looked at the two academicians
そこで、学者の張美輝氏と彭望佳氏は二人の学者を観察した。
They are all Taiwan's outstanding travel experts
彼らは皆、台湾の優れた旅行専門家です。
Then every time they give out the award for outstanding traveler
その後、優秀な旅行者に賞が授与されるたびに、
Wow, many Beiyun girls and Zhongshan Linggao children will go to take pictures with him
わあ、北雲と中山陵高の多くの女の子が彼と一緒に写真を撮りに行きます
The reason is because they also hope that they can be a good scientist one day
その理由は、彼らもいつか良い科学者になりたいと願っているからです。
Then human health and well-being can be improved
そうすれば人間の健康と福祉は改善されるでしょう
Professor Zhang Meihui is such a person who is very kind to patients.
張美輝先生は患者に対してとても優しい方です。
academic research is well done
学術研究はよく行われています
Moreover, the field of dedication to mankind is quite large.
さらに、人類への貢献の分野は非常に広いです。
Then he graduated from the Department of Medicine, National Taiwan University School of Medicine
その後、国立台湾大学医学部医学科を卒業しました。
Physician who once went to the US UCLA Single Pediatric Changwei Hepatobiliary Nutrition for training
かつて米国のUCLAに研修に行った医師 チャンウェイ肝胆道栄養学単科
Then he has published quite a lot of papers in the past
彼は過去にかなりの数の論文を発表しています。
he is a pediatrician
彼は小児科医です
So everyone focuses on childhood diseases
だから誰もが小児疾患に注目する
Especially research on hepatitis and liver cancer
特に肝炎と肝がんに関する研究
what has he posted so far
彼はこれまでに何を投稿しましたか
More than 400 papers
400以上の論文
These papers were published in the well-known
これらの論文は有名な雑誌に掲載されました。
Journal of Forestry Medicine
森林医学ジャーナル
like the sunningland journal of medicine
サニングランド医学ジャーナルのように
Journal of the American Medical Association
アメリカ医師会雑誌
Or journals of small subjects, etc.
あるいは小さなテーマの雑誌など。
is a fairly well-known journal
かなり有名な雑誌です
And it has been cited quite a lot
そしてかなり引用されてる
everyone can see
誰もが見ることができます
Its research skills are quite profound
その研究スキルは非常に奥深いです
In addition to research on hepatitis and liver cancer
肝炎や肝臓がんの研究に加えて
In addition, it also created the world's first
さらに、世界初の
Screening System for Biliary Shelter Syndrome
胆道シェルター症候群のスクリーニングシステム
Then this system helps to improve
このシステムは改善に役立ちます
Early diagnosis of the disease
病気の早期診断
Then also prolong the survival rate
そうすれば生存率も伸びる
So the care of the sick
それで病人の世話
Provides many good benefits
多くの良いメリットを提供します
it's not easy
簡単ではない
Professor Zhang also served as the
張教授は、
many important positions
多くの重要なポジション
Including the director of the small department of the medical school and the hospital
医学部や病院の小さな部門の責任者を含む
Then the chairman of the Taiwan Pediatric Association
その後、台湾小児科協会会長
President of Taiwan Liver Warfare Research Society
台湾肝臓戦研究会会長
I'm just a member and he's the president
私は単なるメンバーで、彼は社長です
Then the director of the Infection Center at National Taiwan University Hospital
その後、国立台湾大学病院感染症センター長
And he was also selected as a luxury university
そして豪華大学にも選ばれました
With a visiting scholar at the National Institutes of Health in the United States
米国国立衛生研究所の客員研究員と
Served in many important positions in medical societies
医学会で多くの重要な役職を歴任
I can’t do it one by one. Everyone has this information in hand.
いちいちやるわけにはいかないので、みんながその情報を持っているんです。
Almost all domestic academic awards
国内の学術賞のほぼすべて
Academician Zhang got everything
学者の張さんはすべてを手に入れた
Including Congress's Interpretation Award Special Science Investigator Award
議会解釈賞、特別科学研究者賞を含む
Science and Technology Honor Award from the Executive Yuan Academic Award from the Ministry of Education
教育部行政院学術賞科学技術栄誉賞受賞
National Award Taiwan Outstanding Female Scientist Award
国家賞台湾優秀女性科学者賞
There is also a classic award called ISI Highly Cited Papers
ISI Highly Cited Papers という古典的な賞もあります。
this is an international award
これは国際的な賞です
Refers to the number of times this paper has been cited by all journals of ISI
この論文が ISI のすべてのジャーナルに引用された回数を指します。
that's not easy
これは簡単ではないということ
Few people in the world can get the ISI paper citation award
ISI論文引用賞を獲得できる人は世界でもわずかです
He also received a well-known scientist from the International Society of the Liver
彼はまた、国際肝臓学会からも著名な科学者からの賞を受賞しました。
Hillas Rock's Award
ヒラスロック賞
Asia Jajurko Award
アジア・ジャジュルコ賞
world academy award
世界アカデミー賞
Trust Prize
トラスト賞
and awards from the Canadian Liver Society, etc.
カナダ肝臓学会などからの賞を受賞。
Therefore, Professor Zhang Wenhui is in
したがって、張文輝教授は、
liver
肝臓
Stomach, liver and gallbladder
胃の肝臓と胆嚢
and this aspect of addiction therapy
そして依存症治療のこの側面
have profound attainments
深い功績を持っている
Then we are honored to have him here today
それでは、今日彼をここにお迎えできて光栄です
give us a speech
私たちにスピーチをしてください
saw so many people attending
とてもたくさんの人が参加しているのを見ました
I believe everyone will look forward to it
みんなも楽しみにしてると思うよ
From Professor Zhang's research
張教授の研究より
gain more knowledge
より多くの知識を得る
Professor Zhang he published in a new article
張何教授が新しい論文を発表
A paper in a medical journal
医学雑誌に掲載された論文
It is about children's education and vaccination
子どもたちの教育と予防接種についてです
vaccination against hepatitis b
b型肝炎に対するワクチン接種
prevent liver cancer
肝臓がんを予防する
This is the first paper in the world that says
これはこう言った世界初の論文です。
Anti-acupuncture can prevent cancer
抗鍼治療は癌を予防することができる
this super god
この超神
amazing research
素晴らしい研究
And this study not only
そして、この研究だけではなく、
Pediatric liver cancer in Taiwan
台湾の小児肝がん
Even after he reaches adulthood
大人になってからも
The incidence rate just now is still decreasing
先ほどの発症率はまだ減少中です
Such a classic study
このような古典的な研究
after publication
出版後
the whole world is watching
全世界が注目している
any other cancer
他のがん
Vaccines can also be used to prevent
ワクチンは予防にも使えます
Later, humans tried their best not to understand
その後、人間は理解できないように最善を尽くしました
Discovery accuses police of being caused by Human Spikevirus
ディスカバリー、ヒューマン・スパイクウイルスが原因で警察を告発
So the vaccine for the main human spike virus was developed.
そこで、主要なヒトスパイクウイルスに対するワクチンが開発されました。
So now many girls
今ではたくさんの女の子が
Vaccine against endemic virus
風土病ウイルスに対するワクチン
to prevent accusations against the police
警察に対する告発を防ぐため
The idea of ​​vaccines was first put forward
ワクチンのアイデアが最初に提唱された
Can prevent cancer
がんを予防できる
such an important discovery
とても重要な発見
Zhang Yuanshi
張元石
the research he did
彼が行った研究
in international journals
国際雑誌で
Has been cited more than 1000 times
1000回以上引用されている
There are not many papers with more than 1000 times
1000回を超える論文はそう多くない
More than 1000 papers in Taiwan
台湾での論文数は1000以上
presumably in medicine
おそらく医学分野で
My own statistics probably won't exceed 10 slices
私自身の統計では、おそらく 10 スライスを超えることはありません
Professor Zhang Yunhui is one of them
張雲輝教授もその一人です
He is also highly regarded internationally
国際的にも高く評価されている
So today we, Manor Circle have the honor
そこで今日、私たちマナー サークルが光栄に思います
You can invite Professor Zhang to give us a speech
張教授を講演に招待できます
I won't say much, I will leave the time to Professor Zhang
多くは言いません、時間を張教授に任せます
After his speech, he will have some questions and answers with you.
彼のスピーチの後、彼はあなたといくつかの質疑応答をする予定です。
Then shall we welcome warmly with applause?
それでは、温かく拍手でお迎えしましょうか。
this great wish
この大きな願いを
Thank you very much to that Vice President Chen for such a good introduction.
このような素晴らしい紹介をしてくださった陳副社長に心より感謝いたします。
very dare not be
とても勇気がありません
I also feel very honored to have the opportunity to be here today.
また、本日ここに出席させていただく機会をいただきまして、大変光栄に思っております。
have some discussion with you
あなたと少し話し合ってください
Seniors here
先輩たちはこちら
and everyone
そしてみんな
Ladies and gentlemen, students
皆様、学生の皆様
I also see very young
とても若いのも見えます
kid
子供
I am very happy to have this opportunity to share with you
このような機会を皆さんと共有できてとても嬉しいです
Let's exchange knowledge on this
これについて知識を交換しましょう
this we hope to have some discussion
これについては議論ができればと思っています
I am looking forward to it, that is to say, I hope today's speech can be
楽しみにしています。つまり、今日のスピーチがそうなることを願っています。
This is an opportunity to exchange ideas with you
あなたと意見を交換する機会です
I think my topic today starts from this
今日のテーマはここから始まると思います
Anti-Cancer Vaccines Begin
抗がんワクチンが始まる
Let's take a look at this first
まずはこれを見てみましょう
I roughly sorted out our today's content
今日の内容をざっくり整理してみました
Probably cancer
おそらく癌
and infection and cancer
そして感染症とガン
Hepatitis B virus infection and liver cancer
B型肝炎ウイルス感染症と肝臓がん
and cancer control
そしてがん対策
cancer prevention
がん予防
Hepatitis B Vaccine and Liver Cancer Prevention
B型肝炎ワクチンと肝がんの予防
besides
そのほか
Future Prospects for Cancer Vaccines
がんワクチンの将来展望
roughly today's
ほぼ今日の
The content should be in this place again
コンテンツは再びこの場所にあるはずです
So let's look at this first
それではまずこれを見てみましょう
current status of cancer
がんの現状
Then we start from the World Health Organization
それから世界保健機関から始めます
It's reported in the latest this one
最新のこれで報道されてる
The 2014 world is still reporting
2014 年の世界はまだ報道中です
It seems that cancers around the world have actually been on the rise
世界中でガンが実際に増加しているようです
We all know that cancer is the number one cause of death in the world
がんが世界で一番の死因であることは誰もが知っています
In 2012, the statistics on the number of new cancers in the world increased again
2012 年、世界の新たながんの数に関する統計は再び増加しました。
Probably increased to about 14 million people every year
おそらく毎年約1,400万人に増加
In addition to the incidence rate, another very important factor is the mortality rate
罹患率に加えて、もう一つの非常に重要な要素は死亡率です。
Its death rate also increased to around 13 million
死亡率も約1,300万人に増加
so a very high number
とても高い数字です
Here's a look at the world's most common causes of cancer death in 2012
2012 年の世界で最も一般的ながんによる死亡原因を見てみましょう。
No. 1 is lung cancer
1位は肺がん
It accounted for 19.4%, close to 20% of all deaths
死亡者数全体の20％近くにあたる19.4％を占めた。
The second place is today's theme is liver cancer
2位は今日のテーマは肝臓がん
I'll spend more time talking about liver cancer later
肝臓がんについては後でもっと時間をかけてお話します
This is our national disease
これは私たちの国民病です
The third one is gastric cancer, before the whole world sees
3つ目は胃がん、全世界が注目する前に
The third place is stomach cancer
3位は胃がん
What I want to say is to show you the situation in Taiwan.
私が言いたいのは、台湾の状況をお見せしたいということです。
The words in Taiwan are very similar to those in the world
台湾の言葉は世界の言葉とよく似ています
No. 1 is lung cancer
1位は肺がん
The second place is liver cancer
2位は肝臓がん
very similar to the world
世界と非常によく似ています
In the past, our liver cancer was often the number one
過去には、肝臓がんが第 1 位になることがよくありました。
Now lung cancer is number one
今では肺がんが第一位です
The third place is the section chief and the chief cancer
3位は課長とガン長
The fourth woman's word is breast cancer
4番目の女性の言葉は「乳がん」
That man has oral cancer
あの人は口腔がんを患っている
That fifth place is female is stomach cancer
5位は女性が胃がん
Esophageal cancer in men
男性の食道がん
Sixth woman with stomach cancer
胃がんを患う6人目の女性
That man has stomach cancer
あの人は胃がんを患っている
The seventh place is uterine well cancer
7位は子宮体がん
and male anterior carcinoma
および男性前がん
So this place looks like it's just been discovered
つまり、この場所は最近発見されたようです
this is the cause of death
これが死因です
Of course there are some diseases like saying
もちろん、言うような病気もあります
it's easier to treat
治療が簡単です
The cause of its death may be
その死因として考えられるのは、
Not so many people died
死んだ人はそれほど多くない
But it happens more often
でもそれはもっと頻繁に起こります
Then let's take a look at the situation in the world
それでは世界情勢を見てみましょう
hepatocellular carcinoma
肝細胞癌
The status of this liver cancer
この肝臓がんの状態は
In what area are there more
どのエリアにもっとありますか
This picture looks like a boy on the left
この写真だと左が男の子っぽいですね
Then the girl on the right
そしたら右側の女の子が
We can see that what is red is green
赤であるものは緑であることがわかります
then blue is mortality
青は死亡率です
It seems that neither incidence nor mortality
発症率も死亡率もないようだ
either red or blue
赤か青のどちらか
Both East Asia and Southeast Asia
東アジアも東南アジアも
In terms of liver cancer, it is the most
肝臓がんに関しては、それが最も多いです。
So this is the disease in our own area
つまり、これは私たちの地域の病気です
Liver cancer is the disease of our place
肝臓がんは私たちの病気です
At the same time we can see that
同時に次のこともわかります
relatively poorly developed places
比較的開発が遅れている場所
The economy is not so good
景気はあまりよくない
Its incidence of liver cancer is higher in both men and women
肝臓がんの発生率は男性と女性の両方で高い
So well-developed countries like this place
先進国はこの場所が好き
not so much
それほど多くない
So liver cancer is also a
つまり肝臓がんも
less well-developed countries
発展途上国
It is more prone to these cancers
これらのがんにかかりやすくなります
shown in this place
この場所に示されている
This building core water shows
この建物のコア水は、
Worldwide average
世界平均
is the IQ of the world
世界のIQです
And we are located in East Asia
そして私たちは東アジアに位置しています
So let's talk about infection and cancer
それでは、感染症とがんについて話しましょう
this is our focus today
これが今日の私たちの焦点です
Of course, it can be seen from the evidence all over the world that
もちろん、世界中の証拠からわかるように、
Cancer-causing risk factors
発がんの危険因子
It is often mentioned in newspapers and media that many, many things
新聞やメディアでよく取り上げられるのは、
Carcinogens of various cancers
さまざまながんの発がん物質
Some of these factors are likely to be
これらの要因のいくつかは次のようなものである可能性があります。
There's some really, really good evidence that
本当に、本当に良い証拠がいくつかある
These have really been proven to be true by various studies
これらはさまざまな研究によって真実であることが証明されています
cancer risk factors
がんの危険因子
Then this place lists four
次に、この場所には 4 つ挙げられます
the first is smoking
一つ目は喫煙です
The second is infection
2つ目は感染症です
The third is radiation
3つ目は放射線です
The fourth is the immune matching agent
4つ目は免疫適合剤です
These four are very clear
この4つは非常に明確です
There is already ample evidence that
すでに十分な証拠がある
It really has a very, very close relationship with cancer
実は癌と非常に密接な関係があるのです
like smoking
喫煙のような
it's about smoking
それは喫煙についてです
About 1.5 million people die from this cancer every year in the world
世界中で毎年約150万人がこのがんで亡くなっています
So smoking is really best not to smoke
だから喫煙は本当に吸わないのが一番良いんだよ
Smoking is really closely related to this cancer
喫煙はこの癌と本当に密接に関係しています
And there is very good evidence that
そして、次のような非常に良い証拠があります。
The second is infection
2つ目は感染症です
this is our topic today
これが今日の私たちのトピックです
Infecting him with his related death toll in developing countries
発展途上国での彼への感染とそれに関連した死亡者
accounted for 22% of their deaths
死亡者の22%を占めた
22% of cancer deaths
がん死亡の22%
In developed countries it is about 6%
先進国では約6%
about 6%
6%左右
So infections are more severe in developing countries
つまり発展途上国では感染症がより深刻になる
is a very, very important cause of cancer
それは癌の非常に重要な原因です
Let's take a look at the famous ones here.
ここで有名なものを見てみましょう
Relationship Between Hepatitis B Virus Infection and Liver Cancer
B型肝炎ウイルス感染と肝臓がんの関係
Globally, approximately every year, the number of deaths caused by this hepatitis B virus may be
世界的には、ほぼ毎年、この B 型肝炎ウイルスによる死亡者数は
like cancer or related cirrhosis
がんや関連する肝硬変など
About 340,000 people each year
毎年約34万人
HPV Infection and Uterine Carcinoma
HPV感染症と子宮がん
About 250,000 people a year
年間約25万人
died for this reason
この理由で亡くなった
So the numbers are very large
したがって、その数は非常に多くなります
Of course, the rest is between radiation and immunity.
もちろん、残りは放射線と免疫の間です。
This is all related to the occurrence of cancer.
これらはすべて癌の発生に関係しています。
Then I will introduce to you
それではご紹介させていただきます
Which infections can cause cancer?
がんを引き起こす可能性のある感染症はどれですか?
We have to be very careful and pay attention to prevent these infections
私たちはこれらの感染症を防ぐために細心の注意を払う必要があります
Because it is some vitamins that cause cancer
ガンの原因となるのはビタミンの一部だからです
The first thing I want to introduce to you is the virus
まず最初に紹介したいのはウイルスです
Everyone is familiar with this virus
誰もがこのウイルスについてよく知っています
It is the relationship between rhinohepatitis virus and liver cancer
鼻肝炎ウイルスと肝臓がんの関係です
This may be in the newspapers and media
新聞やメディアで取り上げられるかもしれません
or in the textbook
もしくは教科書に載ってる
You might see something like this
このようなものが表示されるかもしれません
The other is uterine cancer
もう一つは子宮がんです
HPV
HPV
This is also the message that everyone often sees in this regard.
これは、この点で誰もがよく目にするメッセージでもあります。
Maybe you have heard
もしかしたら聞いたことがあるかもしれません
rhinohepatitis virus
鼻肝炎ウイルス
things that can cause liver cancer
肝臓がんの原因となる可能性のあるもの
Maybe everyone has heard of such a thing
おそらく誰もがそのようなことを聞​​いたことがあるでしょう
Less familiar ones might be like Epstein-Barr virus
あまり馴染みのないものはエプスタイン・バーウイルスのようなものかもしれません
Epstein-Barr virus and this 08 hyperplasia
エプスタイン・バーウイルスとこの08過形成
Or 08 cancer and BNI
または08がんとBNI
Historically there have been such reports
歴史的にはそのような報告がありました
It has been confirmed that between the two of them
二人の間には以下のことが確認されています
have a very close relationship
非常に密接な関係がある
Another one that you may not be familiar with is
あまり馴染みのないもう 1 つは、
Human T cells are 08 virus
ヒトT細胞は08ウイルスです
T cell leukemia
T細胞白血病
If this is the case, it may be mentioned later.
その場合は、後述する可能性があります。
For example, in Japan, there are more diseases like this
例えば日本ではこんな病気が増えています
Another limb-throwing virus may be familiar to everyone
手足を投げる別のウイルスは誰もがよく知っているかもしれません
Limb throwing virus because of its very, very many types
非常に多くの種類があるため、手足を投げるウイルス
can cause many diseases
多くの病気を引き起こす可能性がある
Type VIII of which has recently been discovered
最近発見されたタイプ VIII
It has something to do with Kaposi meat flow
カポジの肉の流れと関係がある
Kaposi meatloaf is a cancer
カポジ・ミートローフは癌だ
The last one is probably the least familiar to everyone.
最後の項目はおそらく誰にとっても最も馴染みのないものです。
This one called Mercose Cell
これはメルコースセルと呼ばれるものです
Multiflux virus and Merkel cell carcinoma
マルチフラックスウイルスとメルケル細胞癌
this is very new
これはとても新しいです
Everyone is very unfamiliar
みんなよく知らないんだよな
It is rarely mentioned in newspapers and magazines
新聞や雑誌で取り上げられることはほとんどありません
This very new virus and this very new cancer
この非常に新しいウイルスとこの非常に新しい癌
This is relatively rare
これは比較的まれです
In fact, except for the virus
実はウイルス以外では
Another very famous
もう一つの非常に有名な
everyone is very familiar
みんなとてもよく知っています
It's the pyloric spiral
それは幽門の螺旋です
Many people probably have this spiral feeling
このスパイラルな気持ちを抱えている人は多いのではないでしょうか
Because his incidence rate is very high
出現率が非常に高いので
Your own family members may also have a pyloric spiral infection
あなた自身の家族も幽門スパイラル感染症に罹患している可能性があります
This bacterium has been recognized by the World Health Organization
この細菌は世界保健機関によって認められています
is closely related to gastric cancer
胃がんと密接な関係がある
parasite aspect
寄生虫の側面
In fact, the history has been very long
実はその歴史はとても古く、
I think it should be my student days
学生時代のはずだと思う
That's what the teacher taught
先生がそう教えてくれた
Learn about worm diseases and bladder cancer
昆虫と膀胱がんについて学ぶ
and Chinese liver lizard and bladder cancer
中国の肝臓トカゲと膀胱がん
these two
この二つ
These two family planning insects are actually very famous
この 2 つの家族計画昆虫は、実は非常に有名です。
closely related to this cancer
このがんと密接に関係している
So if we want to deal with a disease,
したがって、病気に対処したい場合は、
We must first understand why it is
まずそれがなぜなのかを理解する必要があります
so that we have a way to overcome it
それを克服する方法があるように
So is cancer
癌もそうだよ
We need to understand exactly how cancer occurs
がんがどのように発生するかを正確に理解する必要がある
For example, we know that this source of infection
たとえば、この感染源は
Then I'm going to avoid getting this infection
そうすればこの感染症にかからないようにします
Then I won't get this infection
そうすればこの感染症にはかからないよ
Infection-related cancers
感染症関連のがん
Let's use liver cancer and hepatitis B virus as an example
肝臓がんとB型肝炎ウイルスを例に挙げてみましょう
Let's take a look at this hepatitis B virus first.
まずはこのB型肝炎ウイルスについて見ていきましょう。
This time a very small virus
今度は非常に小さなウイルス
It's only 3.2KB that's 3200 clips
3200 個のクリップはわずか 3.2KB です
So it's a very, very small virus
つまり、非常に小さなウイルスです
Let's look at the place in the middle
真ん中の場所を見てみましょう
There are two big black circles in the middle
真ん中に大きな黒い丸が2つあります
The two big black circles mean
2つの大きな黒い丸が意味するのは、
tell us it's a
それはだと教えてください
Double bone DNA virus
ダブルボーン DNA ウイルス
DNA virus
DNAウイルス
Nucleic acid translated into English is DNA
核酸を英語に訳すとDNAです
Everyone is very familiar with the thing called DNA.
DNA と呼ばれるものについては誰もがよく知っています。
it's this its virus
それはそのウイルスです
Because some viruses are RNA viruses
一部のウイルスはRNAウイルスであるため
Some are DNA viruses
DNAウイルスもある
The DNA virus is the deoxynucleic acid virus.
DNA ウイルスはデオキシ核酸ウイルスです。
Then you can see that the circle is incomplete.
すると、円が不完全であることがわかります。
It's just this place that's missing a piece
欠けているのはこの場所だけです
So let's say that the hepatitis B virus
B型肝炎ウイルスがあるとしましょう
Its genes are not quite this
その遺伝子はこれとはまったく異なります
DNA virus
DNAウイルス
A tiny virus is very delicate
小さなウイルスはとてもデリケートです
because it uses such a small gene
とても小さな遺伝子を使っているので
can make many proteins
たくさんのタンパク質を作ることができる
one of the most important
最も重要なものの 1 つ
I want to introduce you to this place
この場所を紹介したいと思います
S antigen
S抗原
The protein it makes is the surface antigen
それが作るタンパク質が表面抗原です
maybe some
たぶんいくつか
Some friends have heard of the hepatitis B surface antigen
B型肝炎表面抗原について聞いたことがある友人もいます。
that means it has a coat
つまりコートがあるということです
hepatitis b virus it wears a coat
B型肝炎ウイルスはコートを着ています
like we wear a coat
私たちがコートを着ているように
it also wears a coat
それはコートも着ています
Then his coat is called hepatic facet antigen B.
そして、彼のコートは肝小面抗原Bと呼ばれます。
Then why mention him in particular?
では、なぜ特に彼について言及するのでしょうか？
Because it's him who waits for the vaccine
ワクチンを待っているのは彼だから
He is the one who uses his outer coat
彼は上着を着ている人です
Make this protein and make this vaccine
このタンパク質を作り、このワクチンを作ります
why
なぜ
because if you can
なぜなら、できれば
If the body can produce antibodies against this protein
体がこのタンパク質に対する抗体を生成できる場合
then he is protected
そうすれば彼は守られる
Although he got into us
彼は私たちの中に侵入しましたが、
But our human body overcomes him
しかし、私たちの人間の体は彼を克服します
Then after the antibodies
それから抗体の後で
I won't be infected by this virus again
もう二度とこのウイルスには感染しません
infected
感染した
So this antigen
つまり、この抗原は
This protein is very important
このタンパク質はとても重要です
Then we'll mention that
それからそれについて言及します
How do some scholars discover
一部の学者はどうやって発見するのか
to something like this
このようなものに
But of course before making vaccines
もちろんワクチンを作る前に
will have a lot
たくさんあるだろう
So doing research is very important
したがって、リサーチを行うことは非常に重要です
Because some scholars go to study
勉強しに行く学者もいるから
It turns out that if the human body has this
人間の体がこれを持っている場合、
Antibodies to Surface Antigens
表面抗原に対する抗体
then he can recover
そうすれば彼は回復できる
he can be protective
彼は保護的になることができる
Another one I want to introduce to you
もう一つご紹介したいのが
inhibitory antigen
阻害性抗原
Also smart. He made a medical antigen.
彼は医療用抗原も作りました。
Then this medical antigen is from this called
したがって、この医学的抗原は以下から呼ばれます
This place is called the core gene region
この場所はコア遺伝子領域と呼ばれます
The blue one is called the pre-core gene region
青い部分はプレコア遺伝子領域と呼ばれます
Then the medical antigen is made from the pre-core gene region
次に、プレコア遺伝子領域から医療用抗原が作成されます。
make one we learn
私たちが学ぶものを作る
This medical antigen can be detected in the serum of our patients
この医療用抗原は患者の血清から検出できます。
Then this medical antigen can be tested
その後、この医学的抗原を検査することができます
what does it mean if it is positive
陽性だとどういう意味ですか？
It means that this person has a high viral load
この人はウイルス量が高いことを意味します
So our doctor went to draw the patient's blood
それで私たちの医師は患者の血液を採取しに行きました
When we see that other doctors are positive for antigens, we will say
他の医師が抗原陽性であることを確認した場合、私たちはこう言います。
Then you have a lot of viruses
そうするとウイルスが大量に発生する
you are highly contagious
あなたは非常に伝染力が強いです
It's easy to get infected if your blood comes out
血が出ると感染しやすい
If the mother is positive for medical antigen
母親が医学的抗原陽性の場合
Then this mother can easily pass it on to his next generation
そうすれば、この母親はそれを簡単に次の世代に伝えることができます
mother-to-child transmission
母子感染
This is what we will mention later
これについては後で説明します
Then of course there is another one with a structure very similar to his
もちろん、彼と非常によく似た構造を持つ別のものが存在します。
core antigen
コア抗原
Then he
そして、彼が
There is also an X resistance
X耐性もある
protein of X
Xのタンパク質
It is closely related to the occurrence of cancer
がんの発生と密接に関係している
In addition, he did an aggregation
さらに、彼は集計を行いました
This polymerase is actually its replicating enzyme
このポリメラーゼは実際にはその複製酵素です
it can use this enzyme to replicate it
この酵素を使用して複製することができます
Then let it continue to produce its offspring
そして子孫を作り続けさせてください
Its polymerase is similar to the reverse enzyme of HIV
そのポリメラーゼは HIV の逆酵素に似ています。
very very similar
とてもとても似ています
So it can produce many, many small viruses
そのため、非常に多くの小さなウイルスを生み出すことができます
Then it infects the cells next to it and infects others
次に、隣の細胞に感染し、他の細胞にも感染します。
So if we look at this cartoon
それでこの漫画を見ると
Pretend it's just the hepatitis B virus
ただのB型肝炎ウイルスであるふりをする
If the cells covered by this circle are liver cells
この円で覆われた細胞が肝細胞の場合
That's the virus that invaded the liver cells
それは肝細胞に侵入したウイルスです
Because the favorite place for hepatitis B virus to live is the liver cells
B型肝炎ウイルスが好んで生息する場所は肝細胞であるため
It enters our liver cells
それは私たちの肝細胞に入ります
then it drags off its coat
それからコートを引きずります
into the river
川の中へ
And then it's this incomplete DNA
そして、それはこの不完全な DNA です
Double bone's DNA can be filled by it
ダブルボーンのDNAを充填することができます
becomes a complete circular double bone
完全な円形の二重骨になります
The status of intact DNA
完全な DNA の状態
called CCCDNA
CCCDNAと呼ばれる
Then it goes back to make some
それから戻って何かを作ります
This ribonucleic acid is made into mRNA
このリボ核酸がmRNAとなります。
Then it makes protein on the one hand
それから一方ではタンパク質を作ります
it can do a lot of those proteins just mentioned
先ほど述べたタンパク質の多くを実行できます
It can also be reversed into
に逆にすることもできます
because its replicase is an retrointrogenase
そのレプリカーゼはレトロイントロゲナーゼであるため、
can turn RNA into DNA
RNAをDNAに変えることができる
And then it makes a lot of DNA
そして、それはたくさんのDNAを作ります
and use the egg whites it just made
作ったばかりの卵白を使います
Wrap Its Own DNA
独自の DNA を包み込む
then wrap it up
それからそれを包みます
secreted from the cell
細胞から分泌される
Then go outside the cell
それから独房の外に出て
Then run to the stem cells next door
それから隣の幹細胞へ走ってください
to infect other more more
他の人にさらに感染させる
own stem cells
自分自身の幹細胞
even from the blood circulation
血液循環からも
and then infect others
そして他の人に感染させる
Or infect others from bodily fluids
あるいは体液から他人に感染する
That's how it's contagious
そうやって伝染するんだよ
So if we check patients in the hospital
それで、病院の患者を検査すると
if check it out it has several marks
チェックしてみるといくつかのマークがあります
like surface antigen positive
表面抗原陽性など
That is, if HBSAG is positive
つまり、HBSAG が陽性の場合
That means the person has been infected with the hepatitis B virus
それは、その人がB型肝炎ウイルスに感染していることを意味します
Because he made this antigen out
彼はこの抗原を作りだしたので
Then if the antigen has been maintained for more than six months
その後、抗原が 6 か月以上維持されている場合
Let's just say you got chronic hepatitis B infection
あなたが慢性B型肝炎に感染したとしましょう
become chronic
慢性化する
he can last more than six months
彼は6ヶ月以上生きられる
Then if the person is lucky after a while
その後、しばらくしてその人が幸運であれば
He checks he has antibodies
彼は抗体があるかどうかをチェックする
Then the surface antibody disappears
すると表面の抗体が消えてしまう
then we say congratulations
それから私たちはおめでとうと言います
You have actually become an acute infection
実は急性感染症になってしまった
Then you have recovered
それからあなたは回復しました
Having antibodies means that you have been infected
抗体があるということは感染しているということです
but has recovered
しかし回復しました
become a condition without chronic infection
慢性感染症のない状態になる
or he may not have been infected
あるいは感染していないかもしれない
But he was vaccinated against hepatitis B
しかし、彼はB型肝炎の予防接種を受けていました
like many young people
多くの若者と同じように
Friends have been vaccinated against hepatitis B
友達がB型肝炎の予防接種を受けました
Played under the age of thirty
30歳未満でプレイ
then he will
そうすれば彼はそうするだろう
protective antibodies
防御抗体
Vaccinations can also produce this
ワクチン接種でも発症する可能性がある
The other is that if it is detected in the blood
もう一つは、血液中に検出された場合です。
Hepatitis B surface antigen positive
B型肝炎表面抗原陽性
and antigen positive
そして抗原陽性
then we are in trouble
それなら私たちは困っています
Then your viral load may be quite high.
その場合、ウイルス量が非常に高い可能性があります。
because we just mentioned
先ほど述べたので
This medical antigen means that the virus replication is very strong
この医療用抗原はウイルスの複製が非常に強力であることを意味します
many viruses mean
多くのウイルスが意味するもの
So the detection in serum
したがって、血清中の検出は
In fact, the doctor will know your condition after such an examination.
実際、医師はそのような検査の後、あなたの状態を知ることになります。
Not only are you a carrier
あなたは運送業者であるだけではありません
are you infected
あなたは感染していますか
And your viral load is high or low
そしてあなたのウイルス量は高いか低いか
Then another doctor can test it for you.
そうすれば、別の医師があなたのために検査してくれるでしょう。
How much DNA is in hepatitis B
B型肝炎にはどれくらいのDNAが存在するのか
Then he can quantify
そうすれば彼は数値化できる
How many viruses are there in each CC of blood
血液の各CCには何個のウイルスが存在するか
That is also how many IU viruses
それはIUウイルスの数でもあります
then you can know
そうすれば知ることができます
Do you already have this replicating virus in your blood?
血液中にこの複製ウイルスがすでに存在していますか?
That means a lot of viruses
つまりウイルスが大量に発生するということです
The other one is called the core antibody
もう1つはコア抗体と呼ばれます
Just now we mentioned the core antigen
先ほどコア抗原について触れました
The core antigen is undetectable in the blood
コア抗原は血液中では検出されません
However, it can detect antibodies
ただし、抗体は検出できます
yes representative said
はい、代表者は言いました
if we were infected
もし私たちが感染していたら
If you have been infected in the past or are currently infected
過去に感染したことがある、または現在感染している場合
will have this core antibody
このコア抗体を持つことになります
can be detected in blood
血液から検出できる
compared to other countries in the world
世界の他の国と比べて
Taiwan is considered to be a very prone to hepatitis B
台湾はB型肝炎に非常に罹りやすいと考えられています
and hepatocellular carcinoma
および肝細胞がん
It-related liver cancer predilection
IT関連肝がんの罹患率
Currently in Taiwan if the person over the age of 30
現在台​​湾に滞在している30歳以上の場合
have not been vaccinated against hepatitis B
B型肝炎のワクチン接種を受けていない
Words from generations that were not beaten in infancy
幼少期に殴られなかった世代の言葉
It can almost be said that 1/1 to 1/1 of the people
ほぼ1/1から1/1の人がいると言えます。
has a considerable ratio
かなりの割合を占めている
Both have chronic hepatitis B virus
両方とも慢性B型肝炎ウイルスを持っています
that it lasts more than six months
それが6か月以上続くということ
this has quite a portion
これはかなりの部分を占めています
become hepatocellular carcinoma
肝細胞がんになる
or cirrhosis of the liver
または肝硬変
so these people
それでこの人たち
We all want him to follow up every six months
私たちは皆、彼に半年ごとのフォローアップを望んでいます
One change early to find out whether he has these diseases
彼がこれらの病気に罹患しているかどうかを知るために、早めに変更してください
Liver cancer occurs more in men than women
肝臓がんは女性よりも男性に多く発生します
Approximately 40 to 60 years of age
40代～60代くらいの方
It can be regarded as his peak period
彼の最盛期と言えるでしょう
About 60% to 80% of the liver cells are in Taiwan
肝細胞の約60～80％が台湾にある
It is related to hepatitis B
B型肝炎と関係がある
chronic hepatitis B virus
慢性B型肝炎ウイルス
related
関連している
That's very special compared to other countries in the world
それは世界の他の国々と比べて非常に特別なことです
because I'm a pediatrician
私は小児科医なので
i see my patient
私の患者に会います
How come it seems that there are many liver cancers?
なぜ肝臓がんが多いように見えるのでしょうか？
Liver cancer and nose type liver cancer
肝臓がんと鼻型肝臓がん
of course
もちろん
We will want to do research with him on this
私たちはこれについて彼と一緒に研究したいと思っています
What the hell are these kids
一体この子たちは何なんだろう
their liver cancer
彼らの肝臓がん
Is it related to nasal HCC virus?
鼻HCCウイルスと関係があるのでしょうか？
So when I went to test my patient, I found out that
そこで患者を検査しに行ったとき、次のことが分かりました。
Wow their nasal HCC virus
すごい、鼻のHCCウイルス
The surface anti-inflammatory positive rate is as high as
表面抗炎症陽性率は
almost to 100%
ほぼ100%
So to show our children their
ですから、子供たちに彼らの姿を見せるために、
What about liver cancer?
肝臓がんについてはどうですか？
They are all related to nasal HCC virus
それらはすべて鼻HCCウイルスに関連しています
That percentage is higher than that of adults
すると、この比率は成人よりも高くなります
adults probably
大人はおそらく
60 to 80% because adults also have a
大人にもあるので60～80％
Suction type liver cancer can cause liver cancer
吸引型肝がんは肝がんの原因となる可能性がある
What about our children who hardly see
目がほとんど見えない子供たちはどうなるでしょうか
Suction-type liver cancer causes this condition of liver cancer
吸引型肝がんがこの症状を引き起こす
almost always with this
ほとんどいつもこれで
HCC
HCC
is related
関連している
so
それで
we feel this
私たちはこれを感じます
is a very special thing
とても特別なことです
To explore how the hepatitis B virus is transmitted
B型肝炎ウイルスがどのように感染するかを調べる
how did you get it
どうやって手に入れたの
Why are there so many people in Taiwan
なぜ台湾にはこんなに人が多いのか
with hepatitis B virus infection
B型肝炎ウイルス感染症を伴う
The most important thing is actually mother-to-child transmission
実は最も重要なのは母子感染です
The generation before vaccination
ワクチン接種前の世代
What about those over the age of 30?
30歳以上の人はどうでしょうか？
Their contagion is mainly half or half
彼らの伝染力は主に半分か半分です
About 50% 60%
約50% 60%
In fact, it was passed down to him from his mother.
実は、それは彼の母親から受け継がれたものでした。
Then this mother came from grandma again
そうすると、このお母さんはまたおばあちゃんから来ました
grandma may be from real grandma again
おばあちゃんはまた本当のおばあちゃんなのかもしれない
Such generations from ancient times
古代からそのような世代
it's been like this
このようになりました
Passed down from generation to generation
世代から世代へと受け継がれていく
Of course, another very important thing is horizontal infection.
もちろん、もう一つ非常に重要なことは水平感染です。
horizontally contagious words
水平的に伝染する言葉
That's what we say from contact with bodily fluids or blood
体液や血液との接触からそう言われる
got it
とった
For example, if it is a sexual act
例えば性行為だったら
or contact with dirty needles
または汚れた針との接触
or anything that penetrates the skin
または皮膚に浸透するもの
including tattoo removal
タトゥー除去も含めて
prick with something unclean
不潔なもので刺す
Or is there something related to this
それともこれに関係するものがあるのでしょうか
words of intrusive behavior
侵入的な態度の言葉
At once
すぐに
so-called horizontal contagion
いわゆる水平感染
before there was no screening protocol
スクリーニングプロトコルが存在しない前は
Of course, blood transfusion is also a very important way
もちろん輸血もとても大切な手段です
We especially want to mention mother-to-child transmission today
今日は特に母子感染について触れておきたいと思います。
It's because of mother-to-child transmission in the pre-vaccination generation
ワクチン接種前の世代の母子感染が原因だ
About fifty to sixty percent or half
50～60パーセント、半分くらい
But today we are under the age of 30
しかし今日では私たちは30歳未満です
Have been vaccinated
予防接種を受けています
people who still get beetle liver cancer
今でも甲虫肝がんになる人
Then it accounts for more than 90%
そうすると90％以上を占めます
So mother-to-child transmission is very important
ですから母子感染はとても重要なのです
Python virus which can be transmitted from the mother
母親から感染する可能性のあるPythonウイルス
at the moment of production or before and after production
製造の瞬間または製造の前後
Because the uterus says Xueyi can cross the placenta
子宮がXueyiが胎盤を通過できると言っているからです
that ran into the vile body
それは卑劣な体にぶつかった
So the newborn may be infected by his mother
つまり新生児は母親から感染する可能性がある
or possibly in utero
あるいはおそらく子宮内で
late in pregnancy
妊娠後期
Because of the uterus and so on
子宮などのせいで
This may result in mother-to-child transmission
母子感染の可能性がある
And we look from our data
データから調べてみると
These mother-to-child transmission children seem to be more likely to get chronic liver disease or liver cancer later
これらの母子感染の子供たちは、後に慢性肝疾患や肝がんになる可能性が高いようです
When it comes to this, we must mention this Professor Bisley, who I respect very much
このことに関して言えば、私が非常に尊敬するビズリー教授について言及する必要があります。
Professor Beasley came to Taiwan from the University of Washington in Seattle
ビーズリー教授がシアトルのワシントン大学から台湾に来ました
He set up a research laboratory in Taiwan to study the hepatitis B and liver cancer.
彼は台湾にB型肝炎と肝臓がんを研究する研究所を設立しました。
He knew that people in Taiwan were suffering from this disease
彼は台湾の人々がこの病気に苦しんでいることを知っていました
So Professor Bisley has been here since 1972 when he was in 1968
つまり、ビズリー教授は 1968 年にいた 1972 年からここに来ています。
Do some research on equine medicine and then go back to the US
馬の医学について研究してから米国に戻る
But he thinks Taiwan does have a lot of liver diseases
しかし、台湾には肝臓病が多いと彼は考えている
So he was especially in the middle of the 15 or 6 years from 1972 to 1987
つまり、彼は特に1972年から1987年までの15、6年間の真っ只中にいたのです。
Made a very, very great contribution to Taiwan
台湾に非常に多大な貢献をしました
He found out that if the mother has hepatitis B and E anti-inflammatory positive
彼は、母親がB型およびE型肝炎に罹患している場合、抗炎症作用が陽性であることを発見しました。
E anti-inflammatory is a person who proves that there is a very high virus
E 抗炎症剤は非常に高いウイルスが存在することを証明する人です
If there is such a situation
そのような状況があれば
Then he could infect his children
そうすれば子供たちに感染する可能性がある
That is, we people from Taiwan
つまり、私たち台湾人は、
This condition has been passed down from generation to generation
この状態は世代から世代へと受け継がれています
The continuation has actually been very, very long
実は続きがとても長くなってしまいました
he on this matter
彼はこの件に関して
He has very in-depth research
彼は非常に深い研究をしています
Then he and this Dr. Stevens
それから彼とこのスティーブンス博士
Their joint research found that
彼らの共同研究により、
If a pregnant woman tests out
妊婦が検査を受ける場合
He was positive for surface antigen and medical antigen
彼は表面抗原と医学的抗原について陽性でした
We call him double positive
私たちは彼をダブルポジティブと呼んでいます
The condition of being double positive for both antigens
両方の抗原に対してダブルポジティブである状態
The child born to the mother
母親から生まれた子供は
85% to 90%
85% ～ 90%
become a chronic infection
慢性感染症になる
because other possible infections
他の感染症の可能性があるため、
become acute and recover
急性になって回復する
But these kids are very unfortunate
でもこの子達は本当に不幸だよ
they become a chronic
彼らは慢性化する
then become a chronic infection almost for life
その後、ほぼ一生続く慢性感染症になる
Even the phenomenon of liver cirrhosis and liver cancer
肝硬変や肝臓がんの現象も
This is also a very important discovery of his
これも彼の非常に重要な発見です
because in the future he will
なぜなら将来彼はそうするだろうから
He later argued that
彼は後にこう主張した
In fact, all newborns should be in
実際、すべての新生児は次の状態にある必要があります。
Vaccines are given when newborns are born
ワクチンは新生児が生まれたときに接種されます
Then he brought this concept to Taiwan
そして彼はこの概念を台湾に持ち込んだ
Later on vaccination policy
その後のワクチン接種政策
Select the newborn as the target
新生児をターゲットとして選択します
Benchmarks for making decisions on vaccination policies across Taiwan
台湾全土のワクチン接種政策を決定するためのベンチマーク
And also become the World Health Organization
そして世界保健機関にもなる
Also like this suggestion
この提案も気に入っています
Babies around the world should be getting hepatitis B
世界中の赤ちゃんがB型肝炎に罹患するはずだ
Vaccinations and start at birth
予防接種と出生時から始める
so i am very grateful
だからとても感謝しています
I think our people in Taiwan
私たちの台湾の人々は、
I really want to thank Professor Bisley for his
ビズリー教授に心から感謝したいと思います。
this important study
この重要な研究
Then he did three very important studies
それから彼は 3 つの非常に重要な研究を行いました
Introduce you here
ここで紹介します
The first one is the newborn just mentioned
1人目は先ほど言った新生児です
He later drew a picture like this
彼は後にこんな絵を描きました
to present a brief illustration of his past research
彼の過去の研究を簡単に説明する
Then this Ling is zero years old
じゃあこのリンちゃんは0歳だよ
if he is a newborn
彼が新生児なら
Then he was infected by his mother
その後母親から感染した
In fact, these mothers are all positive for medical antigens.
実際、これらの母親は全員、医学的抗原に対して陽性です。
S antigen positive double positive carrier
S抗原陽性ダブルポジティブキャリア
Then 90% of these newborns
そして、これらの新生児の90％は
Later in his life he almost became
人生の後半で、彼はもう少しで
a chronic infection condition
慢性的な感染症状態
He did a second study
彼は二度目の研究をした
It's next door to National Taiwan University Hospital
国立台湾大学病院の隣です
At that time, the city center made a
当時、市の中心部は
A kindergarten in the inner city was set up
市内に幼稚園が設置されました
Right next to our National Taiwan University Hospital
国立台湾大学病院のすぐ隣
He put these preschool kindergarten children
彼はこれらの未就学児幼稚園の子供たちを入れました
to do research
研究をする
He saw that these children
彼は、これらの子供たちが
He did his research first
彼は最初にリサーチをした
And then he helped him track it down a year later and two years later
そして彼は、1年後、2年後にそれを追跡するのを手伝いました
It was discovered that if these children were infected
これらの子供たちが感染した場合、
Children about two to four years old
2歳から4歳くらいの子供たち
About one in four children are infected
子どもの約4人に1人が感染している
About 23%
約23%
He became a chronic carrier condition
彼は慢性保因者になった
Then he did a third study
それから彼は3回目の研究を行いました
at National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学にて
He draws blood from incoming students at Taiwan University
彼は台湾大学の新入生から採血している
Then in Taiwan college students graduate
そして台湾では大学生が卒業
When the fourth grade is about to graduate
４年生が卒業を迎える頃には
he draws blood again
彼はまた採血する
Then he saw that if he was not infected the first time
それから彼は、もし最初に感染していなければ、
When graduating from fourth grade
４年生卒業時
but saw that he was infected
しかし、彼が感染していることがわかりました
What about him?
彼についてはどうですか？
He saw their new infection status
彼は彼らの新たな感染状況を見た
then he saw them
それから彼は彼らを見た
How did it turn into a chronic infection?
どのようにして慢性感染症になったのでしょうか?
found that they were 2.7%
2.7%であることがわかりました
about 3%
約3%
become a generational condition
世代的な条件になる
So you can see this curve
この曲線がわかります
is along with the horizontal axis is age
横軸は年齢です
With the increase of age on the horizontal axis
横軸に年齢の増加をとった場合
after infection
感染後
A condition that becomes a chronic generation
慢性化する状態
in a reduced state
減少した状態で
So it can be seen that the younger the child
したがって、子供が若ければ小さいほど、
The more I can't stand this kind of infection
この種の感染症に耐えられないほど
His immunity can't overcome the virus
彼の免疫力はウイルスに勝てない
Then it becomes a surrender to the virus
そうなるとウイルスに屈服することになる
become a chronic infection
慢性感染症になる
The condition of being under the control of the virus for life
生涯ウイルスの支配下にある状態
Even later, the phenomenon of liver cancer
さらに後になって肝臓がんの現象も
So I think his studies
だから彼の勉強は
are very far-reaching
非常に広範囲にわたる
That also proves that good research
これは優れた研究結果を証明するものでもあります
really forever and ever
本当に永遠に永遠に
human health
人間の健康
Of course, because we saw children with liver cancer
もちろん、肝臓がんの子供たちを見たので
We also did some research on liver cancer
肝臓がんについても研究しました
Why do we think these children are different from adults?
なぜこれらの子供たちは大人とは違うと私たちは思うのでしょうか？
It takes 40 to 60 years for adults to develop cancer
成人ががんを発症するには40～60年かかる
These kids spent years
これらの子供たちは何年も過ごしました
Maybe six years, seven years, ten years
たぶん6年、7年、10年
he has cancer
彼は癌を患っている
so fast situation
とても早い状況
He's growing cancer really fast
彼は癌が本当に急速に増殖している
Let's just look at these kids
ちょっとこの子たちを見てみましょう
The mothers of our patients with liver cancer
肝臓がん患者さんのお母さんたち
Finding out about our liver cancer mothers
肝臓がんの母親について知る
94% of children's mothers
子どもたちの母親の94％が
It's all Dai Yuan's mother
それはすべてダイユアンの母親です
Said that these mothers are generation
これらの母親は世代だと言いました
Her mother and child instead of a child infected from the level
レベルから感染した子供の代わりに母親と子供
It seems to be the subject of liver cancer
肝臓がんの話題らしい
levels seem to be less likely to cause childhood liver cancer
このレベルは小児肝がんを引き起こす可能性が低いようです
In contrast we have a group
対照的に、私たちはグループを持っています
generation of children we go to track them to do long-term
私たちは、子供たちの世代を長期的に追跡するために行っています。
In fact, these children are often tracked by us.
実際、これらの子供たちは私たちによって頻繁に追跡されています。
Twenty or thirty years have grown up
20年か30年経って大人になった
many grow up
多くの人が成長します
These kids have grown up in fifty years
この子供たちは50年経って大人になった
Half of his mother is the situation of Dai Yuan
母親の半分は戴源の境遇
is very different
とても違う
These are kids without liver cancer
これらは肝臓がんのない子供たちです
Let's study further
もっと勉強しましょう
Using liver cancer tissue for research
肝臓がん組織を研究に利用する
Found that these children with liver cancer
これらの子供たちが肝臓がんであることが判明しました
his cancerous neighbor
彼の癌性の隣人
those are the same people
それらは同じ人々です
His liver cells that didn't grow cancer
彼の肝臓細胞は癌を成長させなかった
81% of those with liver cirrhosis
肝硬変患者の81％
Said that this liver cirrhosis is so fast
この肝硬変はとても早いと言われました
Let's say he's six years old and he has cirrhosis
彼が6歳で肝硬変を患っているとします。
same as adult
大人と同じ
It's about 80%
80％くらいですよ
is the condition that produces this liver cirrhosis
この肝硬変を引き起こす病気です
So children and adults develop liver cancer
そのため、子供も大人も肝臓がんを発症します
seems like
似ているようです
type B liver cancer
B型肝がん
Just don't know why in terms of speed
速度に関しては理由がわかりません
so fast he walks so fast
彼はとても速く歩く
Actually my patient
実は私の患者さん
He had cirrhosis of the liver sometimes at the age of two
彼は2歳の時に時々肝硬変を患った
then a few years later
それから数年後
after five to ten years
5年から10年後
he developed liver cancer
彼は肝臓がんを発症した
just watched him recover from liver cirrhosis
彼が肝硬変から回復するのを見守ったところだ
on the road to liver cancer
肝臓がんへの道
This looks very
これはとても見えます
very sad
とても悲しい
Let's do this liver cancer tissue
これを肝臓がん組織にしましょう
discovered that these children with liver cancer
これらの子供たちが肝臓がんであることを発見しました
Two-thirds of their liver cancer tissue
肝臓がん組織の 3 分の 2
HBV
HBV
It has gone into the human liver gene
人間の肝臓の遺伝子に組み込まれている
the gene of the virus
ウイルスの遺伝子
become part of human genes
人間の遺伝子の一部になる
we mean
つまり
Involved in our human genes
私たち人間の遺伝子に関与している
next to the liver
肝臓の隣
cirrhosis without liver cancer
肝がんを伴わない肝硬変
These liver tissues are about 22%
これらの肝臓組織は約 22%
Hepatitis B virus gene
B型肝炎ウイルス遺伝子
Into our human genes
私たち人間の遺伝子に
but the other way around
しかしその逆
If the child does not have liver cancer
お子さんが肝臓がんでない場合
Probably it is 0%
おそらく0%です
Without this virus, it would be drawn into its liver tissue
このウイルスがなければ肝臓組織に引き込まれてしまうでしょう
so it's very different
それはとても違います
I'm here to introduce
紹介するためにここに来ました
when i was very young
私がとても若かった頃
a story encountered
出会った物語
really very true story
本当にとても本当の話
There is a Mr. Fishing
ミスター・フィッシングがいる
he was on a boat
彼はボートに乗っていた
By boat from Penghu
澎湖から船で
come to Taiwan
台湾に来てください
with his wife and children
彼の妻と子供たちと一緒に
This kid is called Ah Hua
この子の名前はアー・フア
He is from Penghu
彼は澎湖出身です
was referred by his doctor
彼の医師から紹介された
Come to National Taiwan University Hospital to see me
国立台湾大学病院に会いに来てください
because he said
彼が言ったから
There is a tumor growing in Ah Hua's stomach
Ah Huaの胃の中で腫瘍が成長しています
so wish i came to see him like this
こんなふうに彼に会いに来られたらよかったのに
I'll test Ah Hua's blood
阿華の血液を検査してみます
Ah Hua
ああ、はぁ
in his blood
他的血液中
Hepatitis B surface antigen
B型肝炎表面抗原
is positive
ポジティブです
i have a habit
私には癖があります
If this child is like this
この子がこうだったら
I will help his parents
彼の両親を手伝います
have come
きました
just help him check
彼がチェックするのを手伝ってください
found to say
言うことがわかった
his parents
彼の両親
hepatitis B surface antigen
B型肝炎表面抗原
positive person
ポジティブな人
I made him a stomach
私は彼をお腹にしました
Chaotic neck
混沌とした首
I found it in Ah Hua's stomach
アー・フアのお腹の中で見つけた
have large liver cancer
大きな肝臓がんがある
And this liver cancer
そして今回の肝臓がんは
very very big
とてもとても大きい
dissatisfied with the size of his entire liver
肝臓全体の大きさに不満がある
so there is no way
だから仕方ない
That is to say, he is a well-behaved kid.
つまり、行儀の良い子だということだ。
so there is no cure
だから治療法はない
Then I will often help his parents to be a parent by the way.
それから、私は彼の両親が親になるのをよく手伝います。
I was surprised to find that I didn't expect it
予想していなかったのでびっくりしました
His dad also had a tumor in his stomach
父親も胃に腫瘍を抱えていた
It's also a very, very large stem cancer.
これは非常に大きな幹がんでもあります。
At the same time found out that this is a true story
同時にこれが実話であることを知りました
So at that time, I felt very sorry for his mother.
だからその時、私は彼のお母さんにとても申し訳ないと思いました。
Of course his mother is very sad
もちろんお母さんはとても悲しんでいます
because the three of them came
三人が来たから
Turns out two people got stem cancer
2人が幹がんになったことが判明
Another condition that cannot be treated by tacit understanding
暗黙の了解では治せないもうひとつの症状
So at that time I was a young physician
ですから、当時私は若い医師でした
very ashamed
とても恥ずかしい
I'm a doctor who can't help people
私は人を助けることができない医者です
I am very ashamed
とても恥ずかしいです
So I could only tell him that there was no other way.
だから私は彼に「他に方法はありません」と伝えることしかできませんでした。
I can't have a fetus, and I can't do any treatment.
胎児も産めないし、治療もできない。
Just give him a little travel money
彼に少しの旅費をあげてください
just let them go back to friends
友達に戻らせてください
So actually
それで実際には
This experience happens over and over again
この経験は何度も繰り返されます
Sometimes I see two brothers in my family with liver cancer
時々、家族の中で二人の兄弟が肝臓がんになっているのを見かけます。
Or the parent and the child are in the condition of liver cancer
または親と子が肝臓がんの状態にある
Of course, I really hope there is a way
もちろん、方法があることを本当に願っています
can treat patients
患者を治療できる
But in fact, my abilities are very limited.
しかし実際には、私の能力は非常に限られています。
Looks like it won't help them
彼らを助けることはできないようだ
very miserable
とても悲惨な
So I think it should be that we should think of a way
ですので、何らかの方法を考えるべきだと思います
Including such a small child to get such a serious disease
こんなに小さな子供がこんな重篤な病気になるなんて
We should do a good job of controlling cancer
私たちはがんの制御をしっかりと行うべきです
There are actually three strategies for cancer control
がん制御には実際には 3 つの戦略があります
The first is cancer prevention
まずはがん予防です
This should be the best way
これが最善の方法であるはずです
We keep us humans from getting cancer
私たち人類はガンにならないようにしています
how nice it is
なんて素敵なんだろう
This should be the best policy
これが最善の政策であるはずだ
The second, of course, is how we
2 つ目は、もちろん、私たちがどのようにして
After the cancer has been obtained, the person can give him a good screening
がんを患った後は、適切な検査を受けることができます
find him earlier
早く彼を見つけてください
if it was very small
それが非常に小さかった場合
Can he be removed within two or three centimeters?
２、３センチ以内に除去できるでしょうか？
If there is no other way, of course it is to help him with the best treatment.
他に方法がない場合は、もちろん、彼に最善の治療を提供することです。
It is the best treatment. What kind of good method can cure cancer?
最良の治療法ですが、癌を治す良い方法とは何でしょうか？
That's certainly something we'd very much like to do
それは確かに私たちがとてもやりたいことです
It’s just that there are still many unsatisfactory aspects of cancer treatment so far.
ただ、これまでのがん治療にはまだまだ不十分な点がたくさんあります。
There are still many places to continue to work hard
まだまだ頑張れるところはたくさんあります
So how do we save ourselves from the pain of disease, especially cancer?
では、どうすれば病気、特にがんの痛みから身を守ることができるのでしょうか？
Of course we need to find out what's causing him.
もちろん、何が原因なのかを突き止める必要があります。
We have to do the best strategy for him to control him
私たちは彼をコントロールするために最善の戦略を講じなければなりません
In the three aspects mentioned above, prevention should be more effective than treatment
上記の 3 つの側面において、治療よりも予防​​の方が効果的であるはずです。
It's best if you don't get sick
病気にならなければ一番良いのですが
So how can cancer be prevented?
では、どうすればがんを予防できるのでしょうか？
In fact, cancer prevention can be divided into three levels
実際、がん予防は3つのレベルに分けられます。
The first level is for all the people, including everyone here
最初のレベルは、ここにいる全員を含むすべての人が対象です
All people, regardless of age, can prevent it
年齢に関係なく誰でも予防できる
don't get cancer
がんにならないように
This is the best way, this is the first phase of treatment
これが最善の方法です、これが治療の第一段階です
prevention
防止
What about the second episode?
第二話はどうなるの？
He already knows that he is a high-risk group
彼は自分が高リスクグループであることをすでに知っています
Then target him to prevent him
それから彼を阻止するために彼をターゲットにします
there is one object in particular
特にオブジェクトが 1 つあります
we are going to prevent him
私たちは彼を阻止するつもりです
What about the prevention in the third episode?
第3話では予防はどうなるのでしょうか？
he has cancer
彼は癌を患っている
Then the doctor treated him
それから医者は彼を治療した
Then we have to prevent him from relapsing again.
それから私たちは彼が再び再発するのを防がなければなりません。
So the third episode is relatively late
なので第3話は比較的遅いです
It means you have cancer
それはあなたが癌を患っていることを意味します
we want him not to happen again
私たちは彼が二度と起こらないことを望んでいます
But we also know people like this
しかし、私たちはこのような人々も知っています
In fact, inside his body
実は彼の体の中では
have had some precancerous changes
いくつかの前がん性変化があった
Although not long
長くはありませんが
But he is already
しかし、彼はすでに
enter a comparison
比較を入力してください
There may be some changes in this organization
この組織にはいくつかの変更があるかもしれません
For example, he has cirrhosis of the liver, etc.
たとえば、肝硬変などを患っています。
these conditions
これらの条件
So primary prevention
ということで一次予防
we all feel the best
私たちは皆最高の気分です
What are the methods?
どのような方法がありますか?
for all the people
すべての人々のために
Can primary prevention be done?
一次予防はできるのか？
The best thing, I think, is the vaccine.
一番良いのはワクチンだと思います。
If a vaccine can be used
ワクチンが使えるようになれば
If it can prevent cancer
ガンを予防できるなら
that would be great
それは素晴らしいでしょう
he is cheap and effective
彼は安くて効果的です
It also saves time and is not heavy
時間も節約できるし重くない
The second one is to use this
2つ目はこれを使うことです
Avoid cancer-causing risk behaviors and environments
発がんの原因となるリスクのある行動や環境を避ける
For example, we should avoid smoking
たとえば、私たちは喫煙を避けるべきです
avoid alcohol avoid obesity
アルコールを避ける 肥満を避ける
Avoid low comfort facilities
快適性の低い施設は避ける
And avoid lack of exercise and so on
運動不足なども避けてください
is possible or has been proven
可能である、または証明されている
very well documented
非常によく文書化されている
is related to cancer
がんと関係がある
we should all avoid it
私たちは皆それを避けるべきです
It's primary prevention
一次予防です
But of course it's what you do all your life
でももちろん、それはあなたが一生かけて行うことです
Not just a shot
ただのショットではない
The third is of course chemoprevention.
3番目はもちろん化学予防です。
That is to say, use some natural
つまり、自然なものを使用するということです
Now many people are developing
今では多くの人が開発を行っています
Use some natural or synthetic substances
いくつかの天然または合成物質を使用する
such as drugs
麻薬などの
vitamins
ビタミン
Some people say that taking vitamin A or
ビタミンAを摂取したり、
eat some vitamins
ビタミンを食べる
or vitamin E, etc.
またはビタミンEなど。
and eat some healthy food
そして健康的な食べ物を食べてください
or when the hormones
またはホルモンのとき
etc.
等
can be used to prevent the formation of this cancer
このがんの形成を防ぐために使用できます
and prevention of invasive cancer
浸潤がんの予防
What about these theories?
これらの理論はどうでしょうか？
In fact, it is often seen in newspapers and magazines.
実際、新聞や雑誌でもよく見かけます。
some of that is true
その一部は真実です
some of them are fake
そのうちのいくつかは偽物です
there are some that have been proven effective
効果が実証されているものもある
For example, some
たとえば、いくつかの
Lei Hemeng's handwriting
雷和夢の筆跡
It appears to prevent breast cancer
乳がんの予防になるらしい
50% of the preventive effect is
最大50％の予防効果は
Something like Tamoxifen seems to be quite effective
タモキシフェンのようなものはかなり効果があるようです
But what?
でも何？
In fact, many of them have been proven to be ineffective.
実際、それらの多くは効果がないことが証明されています。
So there are many, many clinical trials and so on
非常に多くの臨床試験などが行われています
still in progress
まだ進行中
I hope there will be more chemoprevention methods in the future
将来的にはより多くの化学予防法が開発されることを願っています
can prevent cancer
がんを予防できる
Then here I use liver cancer
次に、ここでは肝臓がんを使用します
Primary and secondary prevention of liver cancer
肝がんの一次および二次予防
with tertiary prevention
三次予防あり
Let me tell you about the prevention of liver cancer
肝臓がんの予防について教えてください
That primary prevention is against
一次予防は反対です
all general public
すべての一般人
that its cost
そのコストが
because the hepatitis B vaccine is cheap
B型肝炎ワクチンは安いから
Then it is also very effective
それから、これも非常に効果的です
then it takes very little time
それなら時間はほとんどかかりません
it only takes three doses
必要なのは3回分だけです
It's just a prick and three doses and it's done.
1回の注射と3回の投与で完了です。
It's probably over from the time the kid was born until he was six months old.
おそらく子供が生まれてから生後6か月までの間で終わります。
The side effects are very low
副作用は非常に低いです
It's the part where the injection will hurt.
注射で痛い部分です。
In fact, it has no obvious side effects
実際、明らかな副作用はありません
Then it uses the hepatitis B vaccine
次にB型肝炎ワクチンを使用します。
Then it is aimed at newborns and babies.
次に、新生児と乳児を対象としています。
To prevent them from developing chronic hepatitis B virus infection and liver cancer
慢性B型肝炎ウイルス感染症や肝臓がんの発症を防ぐため
so this is the best way
これが最善の方法です
that in liver cancer
それは肝臓がんの場合
Secondary prevention is the use of antiviral drugs
二次予防は抗ウイルス薬の使用です
What about antiviral drugs?
抗ウイルス薬についてはどうですか？
It is mainly aimed at high-risk groups
主にハイリスクグループを対象としています
That is to say, people who have been chronically infected with hepatitis B virus
つまり、B型肝炎ウイルスに慢性的に感染している人です。
give it this drug
この薬をあげてください
Those who received injections or took medicine
注射や薬を服用している方
Of course it costs more
もちろん料金も高くなりますが
because it's going to take a while
しばらく時間がかかるので
If you take medicine, take it every day
薬を飲んでいるなら毎日飲みましょう
eat this for several years
これを数年間食べ続ける
So his effect is of course not as high as the vaccine.
したがって、彼の効果は当然ワクチンほど高くありません。
The effect of prevention
予防効果
it will take several years
数年かかります
that sometimes there are some side effects
時々副作用があること
Like injections of interferon, there will be some obvious side effects
インターフェロン注射と同様、明らかな副作用がいくつかあります
What about taking medicine?
薬を飲むのはどうですか？
some few equal side effects
いくつかの同等の副作用
most people are
ほとんどの人は
no obvious side effects
明らかな副作用はない
However, there may be resistance
ただし抵抗があるかもしれない
Then this is mainly for the prevention of chronic infection
それから、これは主に慢性感染症の予防のためです
he produces
彼がプロデュースする
The phenomenon of liver cancer
肝臓がんという現象
What about tertiary prevention?
三次予防についてはどうでしょうか？
people who have had cancer
がんを患った人
Then use this antiviral drug
それならこの抗ウイルス薬を使ってください
hope he can prevent him
彼が彼を阻止できることを願っています
Do not relapse
再発しないように
That is also using the same
それも同じものを使っています
use this antiviral drug
この抗ウイルス薬を使用してください
Injections or medication
注射とか薬とか
So his side effects and his cost effects, etc.
つまり、彼の副作用と費用効果などです。
are also very similar
もよく似ています
But what?
でも何？
Among them, his effect should be the worst.
その中でも彼の影響は最悪のはずだ。
because he has got cancer
彼は癌を患っているから
had cancer
癌を患っていた
So in this prevention of relapse
そこで今回の再発予防では、
The effect will be more limited
効果はさらに限定的になります
So, we use antiviral drugs
そこで、抗ウイルス薬を使用します
Drugs for the prevention of secondary or tertiary liver cancer
二次性または三次性肝がんの予防薬
It has been shown to slow the severity of the disease
病気の重症化を遅らせることが証明されています
can slow down the progression of the disease
病気の進行を遅らせることができる
So especially for people with liver cirrhosis to prevent liver cancer
したがって、特に肝硬変患者にとっては、肝臓がんを予防するために
it helps
助けになる
It's a problem because of the antiviral drugs we're currently using
私たちが現在使用している抗ウイルス薬が原因で問題になっています
In fact, it is not the most ideal
実際、それは最も理想的なものではありません
Because it still has no way to integrate the entire
全体を統合する方法がまだないため、
From incomplete DNA to a complete DNA in the nucleus
核内の不完全DNAから完全DNAへ
We just saw that diagram is the so-called template for viral replication
図はウイルス複製のいわゆるテンプレートであることがわかりました。
It needs to print a lot of viruses and produce a lot of small viruses.
大量のウイルスを出力し、多数の小さなウイルスを生成する必要があります。
none of it was removed
どれも削除されなかった
So the virus infection still continues to take medicine
だからウイルス感染症はまだ薬を飲み続けている
If you stop taking the medicine
薬の服用をやめたら
Maybe the virus will grow and recur
おそらくウイルスは増殖して再発するでしょう
it just suppresses it
それはただそれを抑制するだけです
At the same time it must be taken for a long time
同時に長期間服用する必要があります
It needs to be used for a long time like three to five years
3～5年程度の長期間使用する必要がある
So it will be more expensive
だからもっと高価になるんだよ
And if you take it for a long time, you may develop drug resistance.
また、長期間服用すると薬剤耐性が生じる可能性があります。
Although new drugs
新薬なのに
drug resistance has outperformed older older versions of the drug
薬剤耐性は古いバージョンの薬剤を上回りました
medicine comes much lower
薬はずっと安くなる
However, resistance may still exist
ただし、抵抗はまだ存在する可能性があります
so talk
だから話してください
Primary prevention is the best
一次予防が一番です
We come by vaccination of nationwide baby
全国の赤ちゃんの予防接種できます
prevent stem cancer
幹がんを予防する
Arguably the most effective way to prevent stem cancer
おそらく幹がんを予防する最も効果的な方法
so we're going to talk
それで話しましょう
Hepatitis Vaccine and Prevention of Liver Cancer
肝炎ワクチンと肝がんの予防
if we want to say
私たちが言いたいなら
If we are vaccinated
ワクチン接種を受けていれば
If it can prevent cancer
ガンを予防できるなら
that would be great
それは素晴らしいでしょう
Just a few injections can prevent cancer
たった数回の注射でガンを予防できる
Vaccine against hepatitis
肝炎に対するワクチン
Let's make this dream come true
この夢を叶えましょう
Because Taiwan suffers from children
台湾は子供たちに苦しんでいるから
Ratio to recognized liver cancer
肝がん認定率
is higher than many other countries in the world
世界の他の多くの国よりも高い
So we in Taiwan are working hard to invest in
そこで私たち台湾は、
The Pythonitis and liver cancer
パイソン炎と肝臓がん
research on prevention
予防に関する研究
it's very meaningful
それはとても意味のあることです
And what about chronic infection with rhinohepatitis virus?
鼻肝炎ウイルスの慢性感染についてはどうでしょうか?
Most of it starts with seduction
ほとんどは誘惑から始まります
So we're all very mindful of saying
だから私たちは皆、こう言うことにとても気をつけています
The prevention of nasal hepatitis should start from infants
鼻肝炎の予防は乳児から始めるべきです
From the first day of birth
生まれた初日から
In fact, it starts from birth
実は誕生から始まるのです
even we'll mention later
後ほど触れますが
Maybe from the pregnant mother
もしかしたら妊婦さんからかもしれない
It starts before it's born
それは生まれる前から始まっている
Then briefly introduce the vaccination of nasal hepatitis
次に、鼻肝炎のワクチン接種について簡単に紹介します。
It is actually divided into two categories
実は2つのカテゴリーに分かれているんです
Vaccination against nasal hepatitis
鼻肝炎に対するワクチン接種
Can be divided into active immunity and passive immunity
能動免疫と受動免疫に分けられる
The so-called active immunization means that I get vaccinated
いわゆる能動予防接種とは、ワクチン接種を受けることを意味します
Passive immunity means that I have not been vaccinated
受動免疫とは、ワクチン接種を受けていないことを意味します
So I can't develop immunity on my own
だから自分で免疫を獲得することはできない
but i took some immunoglobulin
でも免疫グロブリンを摂取しました
What is immunoglobulin?
免疫グロブリンとは何ですか?
It's when someone else gets sick and gets better
それは誰かが病気になって回復したときです
produce some protective antibodies
いくつかの防御抗体を生成する
Then collect it through the manufacturer
その後、メーカー経由で引き取ります
and after condensing it
そしてそれを凝縮した後
then become a needle
それから針になる
and hit me inside
そして私を中に殴りました
then help me temporarily
それから一時的に手伝ってください
it may be effective for several months
数ヶ月は効果があるかもしれない
circulating in my body
私の体の中を循環している
come help me fight this
これと戦うのを手伝ってください
This virus that has invaded my body
私の体に侵入したこのウイルス
so wait a minute we mentioned newborns
ちょっと待ってください、新生児の話をしました
His mother gave him the pregnancy symptoms
彼の母親は彼に妊娠の症状を与えた
production process extrusion process
製造工程 押出工程
into a fairly large number of viruses
かなり多くのウイルスに感染する
Go inside the newborn's body
新生児の体内に入ります
so we are newborn
だから私たちは生まれたばかりです
within 24 hours of birth
生まれてから24時間以内
going to play this
これをプレイするつもりです
Immunoglobulin blue for hepatitis
肝炎に対する免疫グロブリンブルー
prevent this
これを防ぐ
The virus that has entered the body
体内に侵入したウイルスが
then why
それでなんで
Then why not just get vaccinated?
それなら、なぜワクチン接種を受けないのでしょうか？
Because of vaccination in newborns
新生児の予防接種のせいで
he needs to produce antibodies
彼は抗体を産生する必要がある
he needs a while
彼には少し時間が必要だ
Probably at least a week or two
おそらく少なくとも1週間か2週間はかかるだろう
And to two gifts
そしてプレゼントは２つまで
to a month
1ヶ月まで
In fact, we used to measure
実際、以前は測定していました
after a dose
服用後
Only about 50% of people
約50％の人だけが
able to detect antibodies
抗体を検出できる
So the other 50%
つまり残りの50％は
In fact, it is impossible to measure
実際には測ることは不可能ですが、
He still needs a second dose and a third dose.
まだ2回目と3回目の接種が必要だ。
and he will last forever
そして彼は永遠に続くだろう
must rely on the third dose
3回目の投与に頼らなければならない
to be truly durable
本当に耐久性があること
In the History of the Invention of the Making of Hepatitis B
B型肝炎の発明の歴史の中で
it has two generations of vaccines
2世代のワクチンがある
The first generation is made of plasma
第一世代はプラズマでできている
is to treat patients who already have hepatitis B
すでにB型肝炎に感染している患者を治療することです
chronic hepatitis
慢性肝炎
A person with a lot of viruses in his body
体内にウイルスをたくさん持っている人
His blood is used for this vaccine
彼の血液はこのワクチンに使用されます
save it
それを保存
The second generation is genetically engineered
第二世代は遺伝子組み換えされている
just avoid the blood
ただ血を避けてください
Use this genetic engineering method to make
この遺伝子工学的手法を利用して、
relatively avoided
比較的避けられる
conditions that may contaminate the virus
ウイルスに感染する可能性のある条件
situation
シチュエーション
That mentions this hepatitis B surface antigen
このB型肝炎表面抗原について言及しています
And the hepatitis B virus
そしてB型肝炎ウイルス
we must mention this
これについて言及しなければなりません
Professor Bramberg
布蘭伯格教授
Because he is the historical
彼は歴史上の人物だから
The person who discovered this hepatitis B surface antigen
このB型肝炎表面抗原を発見した人
He was originally researching
彼はもともと研究していました
some genetic diseases
いくつかの遺伝病
But he also travels all over the world
しかし彼はまた世界中を旅します
For example, he went to Australia
たとえば、彼はオーストラリアに行きました
to study this native
このネイティブを勉強する
his native
彼の出身地
Take their blood and find a new antigen
彼らの血液を採取して新しい抗原を見つけます
He called it the Australian Antigen
彼はそれをオーストラリア抗原と呼んだ
He found that the Australian antigens were the same as those in the United States
彼はオーストラリアの抗原が米国の抗原と同じであることを発見した
The leukemia patients he collected
彼が集めた白血病患者たち
and some mediterranean patients
地中海の血を引く患者もいる
some antigens in his blood
彼の血液中にいくつかの抗原がある
He doesn't know what it is, both are the same thing
彼にはそれが何なのか分からない、どちらも同じことだ
Later, further research found that
その後のさらなる研究により、
original Australian antigen
オリジナルのオーストラリア抗原
He is actually closely related to hepatitis
実は肝炎と密接な関係がある
And it turned out that he was closely related to hepatitis B
そしてB型肝炎と密接な関係があることが判明
More evidence that he is the so-called hepatitis B surface antigen
彼がいわゆるB型肝炎表面抗原であるというさらなる証拠
It's the surface antigen we just mentioned
それは先ほど述べた表面抗原です
He also knew that later he found out that
彼もそれを知っていましたが、後で知ったのです
If antibodies to surface antigens are available
表面抗原に対する抗体が入手可能な場合
He's just saying he already has protective antibodies.
彼は防御抗体をすでに持っていると言っているだけです。
So he was in 1976
つまり彼は1976年にいた
In 1965 he published a paper
1965年に彼は論文を発表した
He won the Nobel Prize in 1976
彼は1976年にノーベル賞を受賞した
the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine
ノーベル生理学・医学賞
while speaking
話しながら
What about the person who actually invented the vaccine?
実際にワクチンを発明した人物はどうなるのでしょうか？
It's Hearman. It's Dr. Hearman.
ハーマンです、ハーマン博士です。
Dr Hillman he's very smart
ヒルマン博士、彼はとても賢いです
He has made many kinds of vaccines in his life
彼はこれまでにさまざまな種類のワクチンを作ってきた
Not just the hepatitis B vaccine
B型肝炎ワクチンだけではない
then he has a hypothesis
そこで彼には仮説がある
he very cleverly thought of saying
彼はとても賢くこう言うことを考えた
If we take hepatitis B
B型肝炎にかかった場合
Surface antigen, this protein hits the human body
表面抗原、このタンパク質は人体を攻撃します
Does the human body produce antibodies?
人間の体は抗体を生成しますか?
Then is it possible to protect this person?
それでこの人を守ることはできるのか？
not infected
感染していない
he assumes
彼は仮定する
He made a bold hypothesis
彼は大胆な仮説を立てた
Actually no one ever said that
実際にはそんなこと誰も言ってないよ
Then he not only assumes
すると彼はこう仮定するだけでなく、
and he does
そして彼はそうします
He realizes his ideal
彼は自分の理想を実現する
He took some patient's serum
彼は患者の血清を採取した
Chronic infection that already has that infection
すでに感染している慢性感染症
A person with a lot of viruses in his body
体内にウイルスをたくさん持っている人
his blood
彼の血
take him out
彼を連れ出す
Then use three treatment methods to remove sanitary objects
次に、3 つの処理方法を使用して衛生物を除去します。
pepsin
ペプシン
Digestive efficiency
消化効率
Then use the urine count
次に、尿の数を使用します
he used fake punches
彼は偽のパンチを使った
He went to make him the dimensional creature
彼は彼を次元の生き物にするために行った
devitrification
失透
He made his infection no longer exist
彼は感染症をもはや存在させなかった
Then he does strict filtering
次に、彼は厳密なフィルタリングを実行します
then do this
それからこれをしてください
The vaccine he felt was safe
彼が安全だと感じたワクチン
But when he made it, no one dared to use it.
しかし、彼がそれを作ったとき、誰もそれを使おうとはしませんでした。
Because it's made from a patient
患者さんから作ったものだから
Then he went through a lot of procedures
それから彼はたくさんの手続きを経ました
Of course he also went to convince a lot of people
もちろん彼は多くの人を説得しに行きました
Then he used this in the United States
それから彼はこれをアメリカで使用しました
gay
ゲイ
In fact, they are some AIDS
実際、それらはエイズの一種です
Then I thought it must be AIDS patients
それから私はそれはエイズ患者に違いないと思いました
Then they prevent this
その後、彼らはこれを防ぎます
that he found effective
彼が効果的だと感じたこと
Of course this is
もちろんこれは
Later, Professor Beasley and the others introduced
その後、ビーズリー教授らが紹介した。
Want to come to Taiwan to do clinical work
台湾に来て臨床の仕事をしたい
Give this baby in Taiwan a shot
台湾のこの赤ちゃんにショットを与えてください
Of course, Taiwan also encountered great resistance.
もちろん台湾も大きな抵抗に遭いました。
How Taiwanese Babies Can Become
台湾の赤ちゃんはどうやって成長するのか
The guinea pig of the world
世界のモルモット
so this is
それでこれは
Doing these experiments for the first time in the past
過去に初めてこのような実験を行った
people work very hard
人々はとても一生懸命働きます
But they are also very
しかし、彼らもまた非常に
we admire them
私たちは彼らを賞賛します
also very great
とても素晴らしい
Valenzuela later taught Dr.
バレンズエラさんは後に博士に教えた。
they these
彼らはこれら
they have this
彼らはこれを持っています
Scientific progress can be done with genetic engineering
科学の進歩は遺伝子工学によって実現できる
Use this filial mother fungus
この親孝行な母菌を使ってください
Use that EcoLine
そのエコラインを使用してください
coli
大腸菌
filial mother fungus
親孝行な母菌
can do this genetic engineering
この遺伝子操作ができる
Then mass production of protein
そしてタンパク質を大量生産
so they thought
そこで彼らは考えた
Then we will do the second generation
じゃあ第二世代もやろう
Genetically engineered vaccines
遺伝子組み換えワクチン
So the one on the left is the first generation vaccine
左側が第一世代のワクチンです
Take a look with an electron microscope
電子顕微鏡で見てみる
Particles with many surface antigens
表面抗原を多く含む粒子
The one on the right is the second generation
右が二代目です
genetically engineered vaccine
遺伝子組み換えワクチン
He used this filial mother fungus to do a lot of
彼はこの親孝行な母菌を使って、さまざまなことを行いました。
barrel by barrel production
バレルごとの生産
made very similar
非常に似たように作られた
Hepatitis B surface antigen particles
B型肝炎表面抗原的顆粒
one by one
一つずつ
If we take out the patient's serum
患者の血清を取り出したら
Particles, but he still has the virus
粒子はあるが、彼はまだウイルスを持っている
Elongated hepatitis B surface
細長いB型肝炎の表面
So we see that he is genetically engineered
したがって、彼は遺伝子操作されていることがわかります
The gene of this type B liver heart surface antigen
このB型肝心臓表面抗原の遺伝子
put it in the yeast
イーストの中に入れます
Then in the body of the yeast
そして酵母の体内では
just give him a lot of stretching
彼にたくさんストレッチをしてあげてください
and harvest lots and lots of yeast
そしてたくさんの酵母を収穫します
Then save this
それからこれを保存してください
Hepatic heart surface antigen type B protein
肝心臓表面抗原 B 型タンパク質
become like this
こうなる
So the vaccine itself is relatively
したがって、ワクチン自体は比較的
I feel that everyone is more at ease
みんながもっと安心できる気がする
Because he didn't do it from the patient's blood
患者の血液から作ったわけではないから
He used this method of true gene preservation
彼はこの真の遺伝子保存方法を使用しました
So there is no genetic material from the virus
つまり、ウイルスからの遺伝物質は存在しない
no DNA
DNAがない
So it's safer
だからより安全です
So we can see from the picture on the left
したがって、左の写真からわかるように、
Hepatic heart surface antigen type B
肝心臓表面抗原 B 型
There is no gene for the whole type B liver heart
B型肝心臓全体の遺伝子は存在しない
only surface antigens
表面抗原のみ
Then he put this coliform
それから彼はこの大腸菌群を入れました
Then put it in the yeast
それをイーストに入れます
Then you can stretch a lot
そうすると、かなりストレッチできるよ
Then he went through some storage and transformation processes
その後、いくつかの保管と変換のプロセスを経ました。
add some vice jockey and so on
副騎手を追加するなど
and finally mass-produced
そしてついに量産できるようになります
send all over the world
世界中に送る
to fight like this
こうやって戦うのは
The second generation of genetic engineering hospitals is more advanced than the first generation
第 2 世代の遺伝子工学病院は第 1 世代よりもさらに進んでいます。
Everyone is more at ease
みんながもっと安心して
But here, if there are friends born between 1984 and 1992,
しかしここで、1984年から1992年の間に生まれた友人がいるとしたら、
In fact, you are all playing the first generation.
実は皆さん初代をプレイしているんです。
It's the original first generation
初代初代ですよ
But it's all good, right?
でも、大丈夫ですよね？
all very safe
すべてとても安全です
It's actually very safe
実はとても安全なんです
Why?
なぜ？
Because the first generation was also tested by that chimpanzee
初代もあのチンパンジーに試されたんだから
So chimps don't get sick
チンパンジーが病気にならないように
that's okay
大丈夫
It means that in this vaccine, the infectious substances including HIV have been removed
このワクチンではHIVを含む感染性物質が除去されていることを意味します
So this hepatitis B vaccine
それで、このB型肝炎ワクチンは
It is the first successful anti-cancer vaccine in humans
人類で初めて成功した抗がんワクチンです
Then there are many advantages of using this vaccine to prevent cancer
このワクチンを使用して癌を予防することには多くの利点があります
because it is a primary prevention
一次予防なので
so it can target all people
すべての人を対象にできるので
All people can be prevented from infection
すべての人が感染を防ぐことができる
never happen to this kid
この子には決して起こらない
I'm fine like this
私はこのままで大丈夫です
So this is really a plus for all
これは本当にすべての人にとってプラスです
A very good approach for all the populace
すべての国民にとって非常に良いアプローチ
and it's cheap
そして安いです
also very safe
とても安全です
I just mentioned that it saves time
時間の節約になると先ほど言いました
It is three injections. In the early days, it was four injections and later it became three injections.
3回の注射ですが、最初は4回でしたが、その後は3回になりました。
very efficient
非常に効率的
Its anti-cancer benefits will be mentioned later
抗がん効果については後述します
The benefit is quite good
メリットはかなり良い
and can be easily implemented
そして簡単に実装できます
In fact, there is no one way to prevent cancer
実際、がんを予防する唯一の方法はありません
works as well as this
これも同様に機能します
so really good
とても良い
and it's a routine that can be put into babies
そしてそれは赤ちゃんにも取り入れられるルーチンです
inside the vaccination
ワクチン接種の中で
There is a rule to get various vaccines
各種ワクチン接種にはルールがあります
Vaccines that include this type B liver cancer
このB型肝がんを含むワクチン
it can also
それもできます
There are some cancer vaccines like the uterine checkpoint vaccine
子宮チェックポイントワクチンのようながんワクチンもあります
it will be available to students in schools
学校の生徒が利用できるようになります
For example, a large number of students in girls' schools are beaten
例えば、女子校では多数の生徒が殴られている。
Playing in school is still very good
学校で遊ぶのはまだとても良いです
Easy to hit, you can hit a lot
打ちやすい、たくさん打てる
so how to prove
それで、どうやって証明するか
or how to design
またはデザインの仕方
a good cancer
良い癌
What about the vaccine?
ワクチンはどうですか？
It must at least meet the following three points
少なくとも以下の3点を満たしている必要があります
First
初め
this vaccine you made
あなたが作ったこのワクチン
against a creature?
生き物に対して？
To prove that this dimensional creature is
この次元生物が存在することを証明するために
cancers you want to prevent
予防したいがん
There is a very close causal relationship
非常に密接な因果関係がある
For example, if the hepatitis B virus is the dimensional organism
例えば、B型肝炎ウイルスが次元生物だとすると、
Then we have to prove that hepatitis B, a vitamin
次に、ビタミンB型肝炎であることを証明する必要があります。
is closely related to liver cancer
肝臓がんと密接な関係がある
this is the most important point
これが最も重要な点です
They have a relationship so you can prevent it
彼らには関係があるので、それを防ぐことができます
and then become a vaccine against cancer
そして癌に対するワクチンになる
The second thing to prove is that
2番目に証明すべきことは、
The vaccine itself is really hit
ワクチン自体は本当に打撃を受けている
Effective in preventing the infection of this vitamin
このビタミンの感染予防に効果的です
like the hepatitis B vaccine
B型肝炎ワクチンのように
Is it really possible to prevent
本当に防ぐことができるのか
Hepatitis B virus infection
B型肝炎ウイルス感染症
We're going to prove that it really works
それが本当に機能することを証明してみます
We'll present some evidence later
後でいくつかの証拠を提示します
show everyone
みんなに見せて
The third one is of course very important
3番目はもちろん非常に重要です
That means we got the vaccine
つまりワクチンを入手したということだ
Can prevent the infection of this vitamin
このビタミンの感染を防ぐことができます
That's really going to prevent the infection in the end.
それが結果的に感染を防ぐことにつながります。
rather than just being able to prevent that
それを防ぐことができるだけではなく
There is no way to prevent this infection
この感染症を防ぐ方法はありません
it's not that hard
それはそれほど難しいことではありません
So we say the hepatitis B vaccine
つまりB型肝炎ワクチンと言うのです
Can really prevent liver cancer
本当に肝臓がんを予防できる
We're going to come up with real evidence to prove it
それを証明する本物の証拠を見つけ出すつもりだ
After satisfying these three characteristics
この３つの特徴を満たした上で、
can we say
言ってもいいですか
This should be a successful hampered vaccine
これは阻止ワクチンとして成功するはずだ
so let's see
それでは見てみましょう
Because Taiwan is the first country in the world to implement
台湾は世界で最初に導入した国だから
Full blown newborn
本格的な新生児
Countries that have completed liver cancer vaccines
肝がんワクチン接種を完了した国
So we have this opportunity to study
そこで私たちは勉強するこの機会をいただきました
Is it real
本当ですか
Bixing liver cancer vaccine can hinder
混合肝がんワクチンは障害を引き起こす可能性がある
This is from July 1, 1984
これは1984年7月1日のものです
So July 1, 1984
それで1984年7月1日
What about babies born after the 1st?
1日以降に生まれた赤ちゃんはどうなりますか？
There is a chance to get the vaccine against Bixing liver cancer
ビクシング肝がんに対するワクチンを接種できるチャンスがある
That mentions the whole of Taiwan
それは台湾全土を指します
Bixing Liver Cancer Vaccine
ビキシング肝がんワクチン
start building this policy
このポリシーの構築を開始します
We want to thank many predecessors
たくさんの先輩方に感謝したいです
many people
多くの人々
In the middle, I think what I just mentioned
その真ん中で、先ほど申し上げたようなことだと思います。
Professor Bisri's contribution is really great
Bisri教授の貢献は本当に素晴らしいです
Not only did he introduce the concept of mother-child transmission
彼は母子感染の概念を導入しただけではありません
And he did
そして彼はそうしました
He and my teacher Professor Li Qingyun
彼と私の先生、李清雲教授
Jointly achieved Taiwan's first hepatitis
台湾初の肝炎を共同で実現
This clinical trial of vaccination is carried out in Taiwan
このワクチン接種の臨床試験は台湾で実施されています
That of course takes a lot of courage
もちろんそれはとても勇気がいることです
Because many people will not want to participate in this clinical trial
なぜなら、多くの人がこの臨床試験に参加したくないからです。
And what about Professor Luo Guangrui?
では、羅光瑞教授はどうでしょうか？
He also did a clinical trial with another baby
彼は別の赤ちゃんを対象とした臨床試験も行った
Of course there are Professor Song Ruiluo and Professor Chen Ding
もちろん宋瑞洛教授と陳鼎教授もいます。
And Professor Luo, Professor Bisley, Professor Li, etc.
そしてルオ教授、ビズリー教授、リー教授など。
Speaking of more scholars, they all explained to the government and the public
もっと学者と言えば、彼らは皆政府と国民に説明しました。
This is necessary, this vaccination is necessary
これも必要、このワクチン接種も必要
Hepatitis should be prevented
肝炎は予防する必要があります
Vaccinations should start on the new birthday
予防接種は新しい誕生日から始めるべきです
These two concepts are what scholars from all walks of life have been promoting
これら 2 つの概念は、あらゆる分野の学者が推進しているものです。
Then I think the most important thing is our government officials
それから、最も重要なのは政府職員だと思います
It was Li Guoding at that time called Mr. Li Guoding
当時は李国定氏と呼ばれていました
he should be a councilor
彼は議員になるべきだ
And Xu Ziqiu, Director Xu Ziqiu at that time
そして徐子秋、当時の徐子秋監督
Director Xu, I think he is very wise and wise
徐監督はとても聡明で聡明な方だと思います
And he saw very far
そして彼はとても遠くまで見えました
So although there are many, in fact, many scholars have come out to oppose
ですから、多くの学者がいますが、実際には反対する学者もたくさんいます。
including some scholars I know
私の知っている学者も含めて
They objected. They said that children from Taiwan cannot be regarded as the world's first batch of white mice.
彼らは、台湾の子供たちを世界初の白ネズミとみなすことはできない、と反対した。
should not do this
これをすべきではありません
So there are voices against and voices in favor
だから反対の声も賛成の声もある
But these two government officials are very courageous
しかし、この二人の政府高官はとても勇気がある
They start executing like this
彼らはこのように実行を開始します
Make a good plan and start executing it
適切な計画を立てて実行を開始する
And our people, I also think our people are very high-level
そして私たちの従業員は非常にレベルが高いと思います
They are all willing to cooperate with the government's policies
彼らは皆、政府の政策に喜んで協力するつもりだ
Hepatitis B
B型肝炎
Get his newborn vaccinated
新生児に予防接種を受けさせよう
Hepatitis B vaccination design throughout Taiwan
台湾全土でのB型肝炎ワクチン接種の計画
is a ten-year design
10年デザインです
Since 1984
1984年以降
During the two years from 1984 to 1986
1984年から1986年の2年間
In the first two years of the internship, the plasma vaccine
インターンシップの最初の 2 年間は、血漿ワクチン
The first generation of vaccines are played in free places
第一世代のワクチンは無料の場所でプレイされる
There are children of mothers who are positive for hepatitis B surface anti-inflammation
B型肝炎表面抗炎症作用が陽性である母親の子供がいます
So at this time, it is necessary to do pregnancy screening first.
したがって、現時点では、まず妊娠検査を行う必要があります。
Screening for hepatitis B surface anti-inflammatory and E anti-inflammatory in pregnant women
妊婦におけるB型肝炎表面抗炎症作用およびE型肝炎抗炎症作用のスクリーニング
then go see her
それから彼女に会いに行きます
At that time, the experiment in the front area was actually
その時、実はフロントエリアで行われていた実験が、
I also admire Professor Bisley very much
私もビズリー教授をとても尊敬しています
he also said
彼も言いました
Mothers should test E anti-inflammatory and S anti-inflammatory
母親はE抗炎症薬とS抗炎症薬をテストする必要があります
In fact, to the United States today
実は今日アメリカへ
The United States only detects S anti-inflammatory
米国ではS型抗炎症剤のみが検出されている
He did not detect E anti-inflammatory
彼は E 抗炎症物質を検出しませんでした
Then Taiwan has always been
それから台湾はいつも
Over the past 30 years, E anti-inflammatory and S anti-inflammatory have been tested
過去 30 年間にわたり、E 抗炎症作用と S 抗炎症作用が試験されてきました。
I want to say that Professor Bisley has a great influence
ビズリー教授の影響力は大きいと言いたいです
To this day, I still think E anti-inflammatory is very important
今でも私はE抗炎症剤が非常に重要だと考えています
Therefore, the design at that time gave him the child of the E anti-inflammatory positive mother.
したがって、当時の設計では、E抗炎症陽性の母親の子供を彼に与えました。
Immunoglobulin administered within 24 hours
24時間以内に免疫グロブリンを投与する
that when professor beasley passed away two years ago
ビーズリー教授が2年前に亡くなったときのこと
before his death
彼の死の前に
He came to see me about two or three years ago.
彼は2、3年前に私に会いに来ました。
I still need to talk to Dean Chen Jianren
陳建仁学部長とまだ話さなければなりません
He kept mentioning to me
彼は私に言い続けました
You want the people of Taiwan to be re-administered with immunoglobulin
台湾の人々に免疫グロブリンを再投与してほしいとのこと
Earlier, not 20 hours, preferably 12 hours ago
20 時間前ではなく、できれば 12 時間前
The sooner the better
早いほど良い
It has been staring at us in Taiwan to do better like this
台湾では私たちがこのようにもっと良くなるようにと見つめられています
That started on July 1, 1986
それは1986年7月1日に始まりました
Just give the vaccine to all babies
すべての赤ちゃんにワクチンを打てばいい
Since October 1992, it has been changed to
1992 年 10 月以降、次のように変更されました。
The whole of Taiwan has been converted to genetically engineered vaccines
台湾全土が遺伝子組み換えワクチンに転換された
That of course later included this preschooler
もちろん、後にこの未就学児も含まれます
he has catch up
彼は追いついた
There are elementary school students to check
チェックする小学生もいます
What is Hepatitis without injection
注射をしない肝炎とは何ですか
This immunization card needs to be checked
この予防接種カードを確認する必要があります
Those who didn't fight will have to make up for it.
戦わなかったのなら、埋め合わせなければなりません。
Because we are in Taiwan
私たちは台湾にいるので
So we are working with children again
それで私たちは再び子供たちと協力しています
So there is this task
そこでこのタスクがあります
In fact, I also feel that I have this mission.
実は私にもその使命があると感じています。
We should see what the result of the beating is.
殴打の結果がどうなるか見てみる必要がある。
So I'm also lucky to be in
だから私も参加できて幸運です
The spring before July 1, 1984, before the vaccination
1984年7月1日以前の春、ワクチン接種前
in the spring of 1984
1984年の春に
Our children in Taipei did
台北の私たちの子供たちはそうしました
What about a popular end-of-school research with that application?
そのアプリケーションを使って、人気のある学校終わりの研究はどうでしょうか?
Find out that all these children above the age of two
これらの子供たちは全員 2 歳以上であることを調べてください。
About 10% of the children are Bixing hepatitis, surface anti-inflammatory positive
小児の約 10% がビクシング肝炎、表面抗炎症反応陽性
Ethnicity is Bixing Hepatitis Surface Anti-inflammatory Positive Rate
民族性は、ビクシング肝炎表面抗炎症作用の陽性率です。
so very high
とても高い
Then this as a benchmark value is the generation before vaccination
すると、これはベンチマーク値としてワクチン接種前の世代になります。
Then we will do it every five years in the same area
その後、同じ地域で5年ごとに実施します
I found that after five years of red line, children under the age of five will all drop
赤線が5年続くと、5歳未満の子供は全員減ることがわかった
ten years after that green
あの緑から10年後
purple fifteen years later
紫色十五年後
light blue twenty years later
20年後の水色
And what about this orange color twenty-five years later
そして25年後、このオレンジ色はどうなるでしょうか？
I found out that these children who have been beaten are all low
殴られた子供たちはみんなレベルが低いことがわかった
Those who have not been beaten are high
負けていない人は高い
So vaccinations really work
だからワクチン接種は本当に効果がある
Just drop his surface anti-inflammatory positive rate to less than one percent on average.
彼の表面抗炎症陽性率を平均 1 パーセント未満に下げるだけです。
About 0.5% to
約0.5%～
About 1% in these vaccinated generations
これらのワクチン接種世代では約1%
Of course it's high if you haven't played before.
もちろん、これまでプレイしたことがない場合は高いです。
So we can draw a conclusion that
したがって、次のような結論を導き出すことができます
All people forced to vaccinate
すべての人にワクチン接種を強制
Prevented about 90% of
約90％防げる
Chronic liver infection in rhinohepatitis
鼻肝炎における慢性肝感染症
What used to be 10% has become less than 1%
以前は10％だったものが1％未満になりました
that's so effective
それはとても効果的です
It prevents 90% of
90％を防ぎます
but not 100%
でも100%ではない
Actually wait a minute we also mentioned
実はちょっと待ってください、私たちも言いました
What about the remaining 10%?
残りの10％はどうなるのでしょうか？
That's not only in Taiwan
それは台湾だけじゃないよ
And in every state of the world
そして世界のどの州でも
have similar results
同様の結果があります
For example, as shown in this figure
たとえば、この図に示すように、
gambia in africa
アフリカのガンビア
it just dropped from 10% to 0.6
10%から0.6に下がっただけです
Taiwan in Asia
アジアの中の台湾
China
中国
saudi arabia
サウジアラビア
Indonesia
インドネシア
Thailand etc.
タイなど
There is also a marked decline in
も顕著に減少している
what about in america
アメリカではどうですか
like alaska
アラスカのように
that's in europe
それはヨーロッパにあります
like italy
イタリアのように
Wait, there is a very obvious decline
待ってください、非常に明らかな減少があります
So this phenomenon
それでこの現象は
In fact, except for Taiwan
実は台湾を除いて
After seeing the results in Taiwan
台湾での結果を見てから
Many countries have also started
多くの国も始まって​​います
Implement universal vaccination
ユニバーサルワクチン接種の実施
With the promotion of the World Health Organization
世界保健機関の推進により
so almost universal
ほぼ普遍的なので
Everyone has a very noticeable decline
誰もが非常に顕著な衰退を経験しています
The condition of chronic generation of Hepatitis
肝炎の慢性発生の状態
Next we want
次に欲しいのは
Further explore the third question
3 番目の質問をさらに詳しく調べる
Bixing hepatitis status
肝炎の状態
Infections have declined
感染者は減少した
90% and 10% left
90％と10％残っています
So does liver cancer also exist?
では、肝臓がんも存在するのでしょうか？
successfully dropped
無事ドロップされました
So we just want to see
だから私たちはただ見たいだけなのです
children in taiwan
台湾の子供たち
because if we want to see adults
大人に会いたければ
probably until 2024
おそらく2024年まで
Because the adult peak is between 40 and 60 years old
大人のピークは40～60歳だから
Might have to wait until peak season
繁忙期まで待つ必要があるかもしれない
Probably after 2024
おそらく2024年以降
It's been too long to wait like this
こうやって待つのは長すぎた
So we know that children in Taiwan
それで、私たちは台湾の子供たちが
There is a high incidence of hepatocellular carcinoma
肝細胞がんの発生率が高い
So we thought maybe
それで私たちはもしかしたらと思いました
We can use children with liver cancer
肝臓がんの子供たちも利用できます
let's take a look
見てみましょう
Is it already effective for children with liver cancer
肝がんの小児にはすでに効果があるのか
So we see kids from six to nineteen
6歳から19歳までの子供たちがいます
With the assistance of Vice President Chen
陳副総統の協力を得て
Let's take a look at the situation of liver cancer together.
肝臓がんの現状を一緒に見ていきましょう。
found that he said that if we take the birth generation
彼は、私たちが生まれた世代を考慮すると、次のように言ったことを発見しました
is the generation before vaccination
ワクチン接種前の世代です
with his hepatocellular carcinoma
彼は肝細胞癌を患っていた
say six to nine years old
6歳から9歳だと言う
He is 50 million to the fifth power of food
彼は5000万の食べ物の5乗です
Then after liver cancer prevention injection
その後肝がん予防注射後
Birth drops to 0.15
出生率は0.15に低下
So if we take this incidence rate as 1,
したがって、この発生率を 1 とすると、
Then his incidence ratio is 0.3
すると、彼の出現率は 0.3 になります。
That is, divide 0.15 by 50 million to get 0.3
つまり、0.15 を 5,000 万で割ると、0.3 になります。
What does 0.3 mean?
0.3ってどういう意味ですか？
It means 30%
30%という意味です
So he goes from 100% which is 1 to 30% like this
したがって、彼は次のように 1 から 30% である 100% まで進みます。
the same 10 to 14 year olds
同じ10歳から14歳の子供たち
15 to 19 are also reduced to 30% to 32%
15 ～ 19 も 30% ～ 32% に削減されます
So we can say
だから言えることは
70% reduction in incidence of liver cancer
肝臓がんの発生率が70%減少
remaining 30%
残り30％
So it's also very effective
なのでこれも非常に効果的です
Well, we have actually done some acute hepatitis and violent hepatitis
そうですね、私たちは実際にいくつかの急性肝炎と暴力性肝炎を経験しました。
It was found that there is a decline
減少していることが分かりました
just because of time
ただ時間のせいで
so we don't show those results here
したがって、ここではそれらの結果は示しません
So we can say that chronic hepatitis
したがって、慢性肝炎であると言えます。
From our research just now it appears that
私たちのたった今の調査によると、
90% gone, 10% left
90％がなくなって、10％が残っています
Then about 70% of hepatocellular carcinoma disappeared and the remaining 30%
その後、肝細胞癌の約70％が消失し、残りの30％が消失しました。
So we can say that the study of Taiwanese children
したがって、台湾の子供たちの研究は次のように言えます。
What can tell us about the hepatitis B vaccine
B型肝炎ワクチンについて何が分かるか
It should be the first successful anti-cancer vaccine in humans
これは人類で初めて成功した抗がんワクチンとなるはずです
Hepatitis B Vaccine Its Anti-Cancer Effect
B型肝炎ワクチンの抗がん作用
Has gradually progressed from children to adolescents
児童から青年へと徐々に成長していきます
We've just seen 19
たった今19を見ました
In fact, from our recent data we see that it
実際、私たちの最近のデータから、
Gradually extended to the very young adult sequence
非常に若い成人のシーケンスまで徐々に拡張
So such an outcome could be used as a preventive
したがって、このような結果は予防策として使用できる可能性があります
Others are good
他は良いです
or
また
A Reference to Bacteria-Associated Cancers
細菌関連がんへの言及
Should be a good reference for driving
ドライブの参考になれば幸いです
The World Health Organization is certainly seeing these results
世界保健機関は確かにこれらの結果を確認しています
When they were at the World Health Assembly in 1992
1992年に彼らが世界保健総会に出席したとき
Just by saying that to advise all children in the world
これを言うだけで、世界中の子供たちにアドバイスすることができます。
Vaccines are used to prevent hepatitis B
ワクチンはB型肝炎を予防するために使用されます
WHO recommends
WHOが推奨
All babies should be born after
すべての赤ちゃんはその後生まれるべきです
I'm going to get the hepatitis B vaccine right away
すぐにB型肝炎ワクチンを受けに行きます
It is best to inject within 24 hours of birth
生後24時間以内に注射するのがベスト
So he pushes the 24-hour dose
そこで彼は24時間投与量を押し上げた
Of course we also know that many countries in the world
もちろん、世界の多くの国が
Some people live in relatively backward areas
比較的後進的な地域に住んでいる人もいる
They were not born in a hospital
彼らは病院で生まれたわけではありません
So give him a call as soon as he is born
だから、生まれたらすぐに電話してください
Otherwise, he will run away and can't be hit.
そうしないと、彼は逃げてしまい、攻撃を受けることができなくなります。
So in 2012 he counted 94 member states
つまり、2012年に彼は94の加盟国を数えました
are already promoting a 24-hour birth dose
すでに出生時24時間以内の投与を推進している
injection for hepatitis B
要注射B型肝炎
The latest data in 2013
2013年の最新データ
This is in the data of the World Health Organization
これは世界保健機関のデータにあります
Information updated on July 1, 2015
2015年7月1日情報更新
can be seen
見られます
Horrors in 2013
2013 年の恐怖
It can be seen from this figure
この図からもわかるように
It went from 23 countries all the way up to 183
23カ国から183カ国まで増加しました
In 2013 has increased to 183 member states
2013年には加盟国が183カ国に増加
have reached the third dose
3回目の投与に達しました
The entire third-dose country
3回目の接種を受けた国全体
Incorporate into this plan
このプランに組み込む
is to promote
促進することです
The Bishop's hepatitis vaccination in the baby's
司教の赤ちゃんへの肝炎ワクチン接種
Moreover, in these countries of the World Health Organization, it is investigated
さらに、世界保健機関のこれらの国々では、それが調査されています
81% of children have accepted
81％の子どもが受け入れた
Three doses of hepatitis H vaccine
H型肝炎ワクチンを3回接種
So it's a very high success rate
なので成功率が非常に高いです
Of course we hope to reach 90%
もちろん90％に到達したいと思っています
But 81% is pretty good
でも81%ってかなり良いですね
Then this picture is a map of the world
それではこの写真は世界地図です
We can see that in dark blue
濃い青でそれがわかります
That is, it has a coverage rate of three seasons of vaccination
つまり、3シーズン分のワクチン接種率をカバーします。
More than 90% of the countries
90％以上の国が
already has a large area
すでに広い面積を持っている
all blue
オールブルー
very successful
とても成功しました
But we also saw
しかし、私たちも見ました
where there is crimson
深紅があるところ
It is the coverage rate that is almost less than 50%
ほぼ50％を切るカバー率です
very low vaccination rates
ワクチン接種率が非常に低い
what about the pink area
ピンクの部分はどうでしょうか
is also relatively low
も比較的低いです
Probably from 50% to 79% or so
おそらく50%から79%程度
are lower areas
低い地域です
what about these areas
これらの地域はどうですか
In fact, in Southeast Asia
実は東南アジアでは
And Africa is the most
そしてアフリカが一番
Of course we have seen some white countries
もちろん白人国家もいくつか見たことがある
these white countries
これらの白人諸国
Are they all poor countries?
それらはすべて貧しい国ですか？
actually not
実際にはそうではありません
like this our neighbor japan
このように私たちの隣の日本
There are also countries such as the United Kingdom, Northern Europe, etc.
イギリスや北欧などの国もあります。
not very poor
あまり貧乏ではない
But what about their incidence rate is very low
しかし、その発生率は非常に低いのでどうでしょうか
so they just
それで彼らはただ
The country will go to other vaccines
国は他のワクチンを開発するだろう
What about the UK?
イギリスはどうですか？
He's going to fight human breast cancer
彼は人間の乳がんと闘うつもりだ
that vaccine it is very expensive
そのワクチンはとても高価です
Relatively more expensive
比較的高価
On the contrary, it is the loss of the whole people
それどころか、それは国民全体の損失です
All girls lose big
女の子はみんな大損するよ
Japan is fortunate that it is in
日本は幸運なことに、
It should be from last year
去年からだったはず
I got a vaccination for all the people
全員分のワクチンを接種しました
Otherwise they mainly target
それ以外の場合は、主に次のことを目的としています。
High industry insurance group to do preventive injections
予防注射を行う高度産業保険グループ
It's not that you didn't hit right
正しく打てなかったわけではない
Antipruritic
鎮痒薬
method child
メソッドの子
the other this
もう一つはこれ
What about vaccines for cancer prevention?
がん予防のためのワクチンはどうですか？
Just now the vice president also mentioned
先ほど副社長もおっしゃいましたが、
Uterine Well Cancer Vaccine
子宮がんワクチン
Vaccines for Uterine Well Cancer Prevention
子宮がん予防ワクチン
So let's look at uterine well cancer
それでは、子宮体がんについて見てみましょう
uterine well cancer it is
子宮がんです
Five evils of women
女性の五大悪
one of the leading causes of cancer
がんによる死因の一つ
So it's very common
だからそれは非常に一般的です
Around the world each year there are
毎年世界中で、
more than 200,000 women
20万人以上の女性
both died of uterine well cancer
二人とも子宮癌で亡くなった
So there are a lot
だからたくさんあります
Added worldwide
世界中に追加
Uterine well cancer probably has
子宮頸がんはおそらく
500,000 to 600,000 cases
50万～60万件
This is the incidence
これが発生率です
This one just died
こいつはさっき死んだばかりだ
mortality rate
死亡率
About one-fifth of them
そのうちの約5分の1
Is a woman in the Chinese world
中華圏の女性です
So it has a very close relationship with us
つまり私たちと非常に密接な関係があるのです
So the same we use these three principles
したがって、同じようにこれら 3 つの原則を使用します
These three elements to see the status of the uterine examination
子宮検査の状態を見るにはこの3つの要素
Is it the human breast virus and the uterus?
ヒトの乳房ウイルスと子宮でしょうか？
Is there a close relationship
密接な関係があるのか
Is it just its healing vitamin?
単なる癒しのビタミンなのでしょうか？
Human Latovirus Vaccine
ヒトラトウイルスワクチン
Is it really effective to prevent human
人類の感染予防に本当に効果があるのか
produced to prevent infection by this human patovirus
このヒトパトウイルスによる感染を防ぐために作られています。
Prevention of Human Latovirus Infection
ヒトラトウイルス感染症の予防
Is it really possible to prevent cervical cancer?
本当に子宮頸がんを予防できるのでしょうか？
We're going to ask these three questions
この３つの質問をしていきます
Of course, past research has actually
もちろん、過去の研究では実際に
lots of research
たくさんの研究
Human Latovirus has been shown
ヒトラトウイルスが判明
It is indeed the pathogen from the uterine examination.
それは確かに子宮検査からの病原体です。
Let's take a look at this breast pass
この胸パスを見てみましょう
This is what the Human Latovirus looks like
ヒトラトウイルスはこんな感じ
the human latex virus
ヒトラテックスウイルス
It's a sickness without a coat
コートがないと病気だよ
double bone DNA virus
ダブルボーン DNA ウイルス
it's still a little virus
まだ小さなウイルスです
It's about 8 KiloBase
約8キロベースです
That's about 8000 muscle reduction
それは約8000の筋肉の減少です
we just mentioned
先ほど言いました
Hepatitis is 3200 muscle-reducing
肝炎は筋肉を3200個減らす
it's slightly bigger
少し大きいです
but not too big
でも大きすぎない
It is about 8000 muscle reduction
約8000の筋肉減少です
It can infect the skin and mucous membranes
皮膚や粘膜に感染する可能性があります
its epidermal cells
その表皮細胞
but it's also complicated
でもそれは複雑でもある
It has more than 100 kinds of
100種類以上あります
Different lines of human milk soil
母乳土壌のさまざまなライン
Virus
ウイルス
So of course when making the vaccine
もちろんワクチンを作るときも
There are so many different lines to consider
考慮すべきさまざまなラインがたくさんあります
Can I be prevented by this vaccine?
このワクチンで予防できますか?
Then the final compromise is probably to find
その場合、最終的な妥協点はおそらく次のとおりです。
The industries that are most likely to cure cancer
がんを治す可能性が最も高い業界
come as the first choice
最初の選択肢として来てください
Object of the first-generation vaccine
第一世代ワクチンの対象
The human milk soil virus has 8 genes
ヒト乳土壌ウイルスには8つの遺伝子がある
is what this place shows
それがこの場所が示しているものです
From this E1 E2 no E3
このE1 E2のE3から
Then go to E7 like this
そしてこのようにE7に行きます
Burley bacteria is long
バーレー菌は長い
In addition it has two bowl genes
さらにボウル遺伝子が2つあります
Its bowl genes are L1 and L2
そのボウル遺伝子はL1とL2です
This bowl gene was later used to make vaccines
このボウル遺伝子は後にワクチンの製造に使用されました
This bowl gene is responsible for encoding the coat protein of the virus
このボウル遺伝子はウイルスのコートタンパク質のコード化を担当します
capacity protein in its shell
殻の中にあるタンパク質の容量
So it can be used as a vaccine
だからワクチンとして使えるんだよ
algal gene
藻類の遺伝子
Especially the two genes E6 and E7
特に 2 つの遺伝子 E6 と E7
It is related to carcinogenic
発がん性と関係がある
it interferes with the prime group
プライムグループに干渉します
the prime group it was violated
違反されたプライムグループ
This human cell gene transfer
このヒト細胞遺伝子導入
and cell cycle control
と細胞周期の制御
So it will be carcinogenic
だから発がん性があるんだよ
It is very important that on the specimen of human uterine cancer
ヒト子宮がんの標本では、次のことが非常に重要です。
It can be found that 99.7 is almost close to 100%
99.7がほぼ100%に近いことがわかります。
Human papillomavirus DNA can be found
ヒトパピローマウイルスのDNAが見つかる
its genetic material
その遺伝物質
Indicates the relationship between the two
二人の関係を表します
really very close
本当にとても近い
There are many types of human lactoviruses
ヒトラクトウイルスにはたくさんの種類がある
But several of them are
しかし、そのうちのいくつかは、
High-risk cancer-causing types
高リスクの発がん性タイプ
its lineage
その血統
It is the human primary keratinocytes
それはヒトの初代ケラチノサイトです
can live forever
永遠に生きられる
So it means it can cause cancer
つまりガン​​を引き起こす可能性があるということです
If we block
ブロックすると、
Human Latovirus in
ヒトラトウイルス
The very important algal genes just mentioned
先ほど述べた非常に重要な藻類の遺伝子
That is 1,6 and 1,7
つまり 1,6 と 1,7
if it is a cancer-causing gene
それが癌の原因となる遺伝子であれば
These cells can no longer survive
これらの細胞はもはや生き残ることができません
There is no way to survive and reproduce
生き残って繁殖する方法はない
will die
死んでしまいます
So they are also quite directly related
したがって、それらは非常に直接的に関連しています
Carcinogenesis and lack of differentiation of epithelial cells
発がんと上皮細胞の分化不全
is very closely related
非常に密接に関係している
There is no way to differentiate, it will cause cancer
区別する方法はありません、それは癌を引き起こすでしょう
Human Latovirus Gene
ヒトラトウイルス遺伝子
are genes that can be embedded in this prime group
この素数グループに埋め込むことができる遺伝子です
It also causes the cells to fail to differentiate
細胞の分化不全も引き起こします
this phenomenon
この現象
So Human Latovirus and
つまり、ヒトラトウイルスと
Human uterine diseases are very
人間の子宮の病気は非常に深刻です
very close relationship
非常に親密な関係
Then let's take a look at how it makes viruses
では、どのようにしてウイルスが作られるのかを見てみましょう。
See this with this cartoon
この漫画と一緒に見てください
Human breast figure
人間の胸の図
Vaccines Human Mammogram Virus Vaccine Production
ワクチン ヒトマンモグラフィーウイルスワクチン製造
of course
もちろん
Need to have a well researched basis to justify saying
この発言を正当化するには、十分に調査された根拠が必要です
use this
これを使って
This tube gene this L1
このチューブ遺伝子、この L1
or L2 is correct
またはL2が正しい
If you use L1 L2 and trigger it to develop immunity
L1 L2を使用してそれをトリガーすると免疫が発生します
is it possible to fight this
これと戦うことは可能ですか
Can develop immunity to fight against the invasion of this virus
このウイルスの侵入に対抗する免疫を発達させることができます
So take five of these L1 proteins
したがって、これらの L1 タンパク質を 5 つ摂取してください
put it together
一緒に置く
Then make a L1
次にL1を作成します
Granules are Capsule grains
顆粒はカプセル粒です
make a particle
粒子を作る
Then put this 72 particles
次に、これを72個の粒子を入れます
blend it again
もう一度組み合わせます
just make a VLP
VLPを作るだけ
This virus-like particle
このウイルスのような粒子
It is the so-called Virus-like particle
いわゆるウイルス様粒子です
Then this particle is similar to the human breast map virus we saw
したがって、この粒子は、私たちが見たヒト乳房マップウイルスに似ています
Actually looks very similar
実際はよく似ています
much like a virus
ウイルスとよく似ています
It's hollow inside
中は空洞です
It has no virus genes in it
ウイルスの遺伝子は入っていない
so look alike
だから似てる
very similar
とても似ている
That can trigger this Yuwen's antibody
それがこのユウェンの抗体を引き起こす可能性がある
So from this human five poisonous virus
つまり、この人間の五毒ウイルスから
After the manufacturer produced two kinds of this vaccine
メーカーがこのワクチンを2種類製造した後
it started in 2006
2006年に始まりました
Just register in every country in the world
世界各国で登録するだけ
Then introduce the countries of the world
それでは世界の国を紹介していきます
Already more than 100 countries
すでに100カ国以上
introduced this registry
このレジストリを導入しました
is registered with this human
この人間に登録されています
This human travel vaccine can be vaccinated
この人間用トラベルワクチンは接種可能です
virus vaccine
ウイルスワクチン
Started in 2012
2012年開始
Human journey virus vaccine has entered
ヒューマンジャーニーウイルスワクチンが入った
At least 40 countries claim
少なくとも40か国が主張
They're going to do the national girl's
彼らは全国女子大会をやるつもりだ
There are even boys
男の子もいるよ
Like the United States, there are also boys
アメリカと同じように男の子もいる
It is to register the human journey vaccine
ヒューマンジャーニーワクチンを登録することです
and comprehensive
そして包括的な
The Human Journey Vaccine Viruses of All Countries
人類の旅 各国のワクチンウイルス
the virus vaccine
ウイルスワクチン
They are all aimed at young girls as the first and most important object
それらはすべて、最初で最も重要な対象として若い女の子に向けられています
Therefore, you can play if you are over eight or nine years old.
したがって、8 歳または 9 歳以上であればプレイできます。
Most of them were played in the senior year of elementary school or
それらのほとんどは小学校高学年か、
Especially in the first year of junior high school
特に中学1年生の頃は
is three years old
3歳です
girls aged three to fifteen
3歳から15歳までの女の子
Then this vaccine is relatively
それから、このワクチンは比較的
It is much more expensive than Bixing hepatitis vaccine
ビキシング肝炎ワクチンよりもはるかに高価です
But it's really expensive after three doses
でも3回接種するとかなり高いです
Still not as expensive as those antiviral drugs
まだそれらの抗ウイルス薬ほど高価ではありません
Because it ends after three doses
3回接種で終わるから
Some vaccines are even being promoted now
一部のワクチンは現在推進されています
Is it okay to take two doses?
2回に分けて飲んでも大丈夫でしょうか？
because in poorer countries it feels
貧しい国ではそう感じるからです
it's still too expensive
まだ高すぎる
But a small number of low-income countries
しかし、少数の低所得国では
Like not only poor countries like Rwanda
ルワンダのような貧しい国だけではない
After they accept donations from other countries
他国からの寄付を受け入れた後
It can be introduced in 2010 and 2011 respectively
それぞれ2010年と2011年に導入可能
Human Journey Virus Vaccines in Adolescents
ヒューマン・ジャーニーの青少年へのウイルスワクチン
Start doing this injection in their country
彼らの国でこの注射を始めてください
Because we all know that low-income countries actually have higher
なぜなら、低所得国の方が実際には所得が高いことを誰もが知っているからです。
This vaccine should be given to poor countries
このワクチンは貧しい国に投与されるべきです
But these 40 countries are actually relatively rich countries
しかし、これら 40 か国は実際には比較的裕福な国です
How long can it protect after these hits?
これらの攻撃の後、どれくらいの間防御できますか?
Even if we were actually just a moment later we'll mention
たとえ実際にはほんの一瞬後であったとしても、私たちは言及します
How long will this vaccine protect us?
このワクチンはどれくらい私たちを守ってくれるのでしょうか？
After playing, do I need to add more or what?
プレイした後、さらに追加する必要がありますか?
It is more troublesome to add
追加するのはさらに面倒です
Evidence as far as we know because it has not been introduced as long as liver B
肝臓Bほど長く導入されていないため、私たちが知る限りの証拠
So the antibodies produced by the two vaccines
したがって、2つのワクチンによって生成される抗体は
Immunity to this type 16 and type 18
この 16 型および 18 型に対する免疫
Probably L1 has more antibodies to test its antibodies
おそらくL1は抗体をテストするためのより多くの抗体を持っているでしょう
and for this precancerous lesion
そしてこの前がん病変については
Because uterine cancer is easier to study these precancerous lesions
子宮がんはこれらの前がん病変を研究するのが容易であるため、
Its speed is faster and you can see whether it exists or not earlier.
速度が速くなり、存在するかどうかをより早く確認できます。
Probably can last for at least 9.4 years
おそらく少なくとも9.4年は続くだろう
So about 10 years or so
それで10年くらいかな
What about privately priced vaccines?
民間価格のワクチンについてはどうですか？
Presumably his research also saw presumably can maintain the latest reports
おそらく彼の研究でも最新の報告を維持できると考えられます
But he can last about eight years or more
しかし、彼は約8年以上生きることができます
So probably I think maybe ten years should be no problem
だからたぶん10年くらいは問題ないと思うよ
That doesn't mean there will be problems if it's more than ten years old.
だからといって、10年以上経っても問題が起きるわけではありません。
but no evidence
しかし証拠がない
just don't know yet
まだわからないだけです
But of course it will become apparent after a little more time
でももちろんそれはもう少し時間が経てば明らかになるだろう
so what
だから何
what is the future outlook
将来の見通しは何ですか
We see this under-resourced place
この場所は資源が不足していることがわかります
We think he should ask him to help everyone to help him
私たちは彼に、みんなを助けてくれるように頼むべきだと思います
So if there are some people who are not vaccinated
ワクチン接種を受けていない人がいる場合
We want to persuade him to get vaccinated
私たちは彼にワクチン接種を受けるよう説得したい
because some anti-vaccine groups
一部の反ワクチン団体があるため、
The vaccine failure is the most serious
ワクチンの失敗が最も深刻
We in Taiwan should work hard to overcome this problem
私たち台湾人はこの問題を克服するために努力する必要があります
How long can the long-term protection last?
長期保護はどのくらい持続できますか?
That's what we should know
それが私たちが知るべきことです
The current recommendation is to say
現在の推奨事項は次のとおりです
prophylaxis against hepatitis B
B型肝炎の予防
Do you want to add it?
追加しますか?
actually don't need
実際には必要ありません
for at least twenty years
少なくとも20年間は
From our current evidence it appears that
私たちの現在の証拠から、次のように思われます
and the recommendations of the World Health Organization
および世界保健機関の推奨事項
So now Taiwan is facing the biggest problem
つまり台湾は今最大の問題に直面している
What to do to prevent registration failure
登録失敗を防ぐためにすべきこと
Of course, the mother's high viral load is the biggest reason
もちろん、母親のウイルス量が多いことが最大の理由です
Maternal high viral load especially anti-antigen positive
母体のウイルス量が多く、特に抗抗原陽性
mother who is also antigen positive
母親も抗原陽性
Intrauterine Infection Conditions
子宮内感染症の状態
The second is that viruses are also very smart
2 つ目は、ウイルスも非常に賢いということです
it may produce some antiviral some
何らかの抗ウイルス薬が生成される可能性があります
against this mutant strain of immunity
この免疫の変異株に対して
Then let the virus survive
だったらウイルスを生き残らせろよ
The third factor is the prime group
3番目の要素は素群です
It is actually immune insufficiency
実は免疫不全なのです
or it has some immunosuppressants
または免疫抑制剤が含まれている
or its genetic response to these vaccines
またはこれらのワクチンに対する遺伝子反応
no way to produce antibodies
抗体を作る方法がない
then the problem arises
それから問題が起こります
Intrauterine infection in our past study
私たちの過去の研究における子宮内感染症
665 mothers
665個母親
Antigen positive mother
抗原陽性の母親
About 2.4% of her children
彼女の子供たちの約 2.4%
Her baby was born on the first day of life
彼女の赤ちゃんは人生の最初の日に生まれました
Liver face antigen positive status
肝顔面抗原陽性状態
And we tracked them for 12 months and found that they all became chronic and distant
そして、私たちはそれらを12か月間追跡したところ、それらはすべて慢性的で疎遠になっていることがわかりました
So this is called an intrauterine infection
これを子宮内感染症といいます
In our other study, we studied about 583 children.
私たちの別の研究では、約 583 人の子供たちを調査しました。
What if his mother is anti-antigen positive and the mother with the highest risk of surface antigen-positive
彼の母親が抗抗原陽性であり、表面抗原陽性のリスクが最も高い母親だったらどうなるでしょうか
We found that 9.26% of them, about 9 to 10 percent, became chronically infected.
そのうちの9.26％、つまり約9～10％が慢性感染症になっていることがわかりました。
What about if the mother is anti-antigen positive and has the second highest infection status?
母親が抗抗原陽性で、感染状況が 2 番目に高い場合はどうなるでしょうか?
Then his child probably didn't get immunoglobulin, about 0.29%
すると、彼の子供はおそらく免疫グロブリンを獲得しなかったでしょう、約0.29%
Then if immunoglobulin is administered, 0.14% is much worse than 0.29 and 9.26.
次に、免疫グロブリンが投与された場合、0.14% は 0.29 および 9.26 よりもはるかに悪くなります。
So we know that this group is the object of our greatest efforts in the future.
したがって、私たちはこのグループが今後の私たちの最大の努力の対象であることを知っています。
It is the mothers of the high-risk group who are positive for S antigen and positive for S antigen
S抗原陽性およびS抗原陽性であるのは、高リスクグループの母親です。
We must keep his children from getting infected
私たちは彼の子供たちが感染しないようにしなければなりません
So, in this group of mothers, the S antigen-positive children probably have
したがって、この母親グループでは、S 抗原陽性の子供たちはおそらく
10% will prevent injection failure
10%で射出不良を防止
If it is anti-antigen negative
抗抗原陰性の場合
S antigen positive child with original mother
元の母親とのS抗原陽性の子供
Less than 1% of his prophylaxis failures
予防策の失敗は 1% 未満
But of course he also has the chance to become
しかし、もちろん彼にもそうなるチャンスがあります
Acute or fulminant hepatitis condition
急性または劇症肝炎の状態
also pay attention
も注意してください
So we did a prospective study
そこで私たちは前向き研究を行いました
mothers of the highest risk group
最も高いリスクグループの母親
when he was pregnant
彼が妊娠していたとき
The amount of virus in the blood
血液中のウイルスの量
Come test him and find out
来て彼をテストして調べてください
80% of them
そのうちの 80%
very high viral load
非常に高いウイルス量
From the 6th power of 10 to the 9th power of 10 or more
10の6乗から10の9乗以上
very very high viral load
非常に非常に高いウイルス量
In contrast, if it is the second highest risk group
対照的に、2 番目にリスクの高いグループの場合は、
Antigen Negative
抗原陰性
But the words of mothers who are positive for S antigen
でもS抗原陽性のお母さんの言葉
Only 0.5%
わずか0.5%
His viral load is around 6 to 8 powers
彼のウイルス量はおよそ 6 ～​​ 8 乗です
So if we look at the picture on the right
そこで、右の写真を見ると、
You will find that the horizontal axis is
横軸が
viral load during pregnancy
妊娠中のウイルス量
what about his child
彼の子供はどうですか
Is there any performance when the belt is originally the center axis?
元々ベルトが中心軸の場合性能はあるのでしょうか？
prophylaxis failure rate
予防失敗率
will find out that
それが分かるだろう
If the mother's viral load is higher in these children
これらの子供たちの母親のウイルス量がより高い場合
The higher the percentage of her failure
彼女の失敗の割合が高くなるほど
even from one to nine powers
1から9乗まででも
Possibly 30% of children could be vaccinated
おそらく30％の子供がワクチン接種を受ける可能性がある
Everything is a failure
すべては失敗だ
So it's very dangerous for these kids
つまり、この子供たちにとっては非常に危険です
So our suggestion is to say
そこで私たちの提案は次のようになります。
All pregnant women should have
すべての妊婦が持つべきもの
when you're 12 weeks pregnant
妊娠12週のとき
should be tested for hepatitis B markers
B型肝炎マーカーの検査を受ける必要がある
All babies should be within 24 hours
すべての赤ちゃんは24時間以内に出産する必要があります
go for vaccinations
予防接種に行く
when she was born
彼女が生まれたとき
30 days old
生後30日
180 days old in August
8月で生後180日目
Going to get three full seasons of vaccinations
3シーズン分のワクチン接種を受ける予定です
And as suggested by Professor B Death
そしてBデス教授が示唆したように
they should be in
彼らはいるはずだ
Children of mothers with anti-antigen positive
抗抗原陽性の母親の子供
should be within 24 hours
24時間以内である必要があります
must be the sooner the better
早ければ早いほど良いはずです
receive immunizations for Danish injections
デンマーク注射の予防接種を受ける
Of course, what we hope most is to reduce the
もちろん、私たちが最も望んでいるのは、
The amount of HBV in these pregnant women
これらの妊婦のHBVの量
how to do it
どうやってするの
We are currently conducting clinical trials
現在臨床試験を行っております
It was during the third period
3期の頃でした
can be slower
遅くなる可能性があります
Mom takes antiviral drugs
母は抗ウイルス薬を服用しています
and let mom's viral load go down
そしてお母さんのウイルス量を減らしましょう
Our preliminary results show that it is effective
私たちの暫定的な結果は、それが効果的であることを示しています
It is true that the infection rate of these children has dropped
これらの子供たちの感染率が下が​​ったのは事実です
So we say against hepatitis B and other related
したがって、私たちはB型肝炎やその他の関連するものに対して反対します。
These liver words related to him
彼に関するこれらの肝の言葉
We should stop mother-to-child transmission
母子感染を止めるべきです
And the blocking of this infection
そしてこの感染を阻止するのは
It should start from the fetus and from the neonatal period
胎児から、新生児期から始めるべきです
This is where we very much hope to be able to do well in the future
これは私たちが将来うまくやっていくことを非常に期待しているところです
Of course, other anti-cancer vaccines have also been developed
もちろん、他の抗がんワクチンも開発されています。
For example, in addition to the above two
例えば上記2つに加えて、
In addition to uterine cancer and liver cancer that have been vaccinated
ワクチン接種済みの子宮がん、肝がんに加えて
Like hepatitis virus and liver cancer
肝炎ウイルスや肝臓がんと同じように、
pyloric helix sensitivity
幽門螺旋感性
with this stomach cancer and
今回の胃がんでは、
Ibe virus and lymphoma and BMI
イベウイルスとリンパ腫とBMI
And herpes virus type 8 and capuchin
そしてヘルペスウイルス8型とオマキザル
human T cell leukemia virus
ヒトT細胞白血病ウイルス
adult T cell leukemia
成人T細胞白血病
So many patients generate so many new patients every year
非常に多くの患者が毎年非常に多くの新規患者を生み出しています
no vaccine yet
まだワクチンはありません
So we should work harder to
だから私たちはもっと努力すべきだ
to develop these new vaccines
これらの新しいワクチンを開発するために
So in the end I'm going to tell you
それで最後に言います
talk about future prospects
将来の展望について話す
What about the development of new vaccines in the future?
今後の新しいワクチンの開発はどうなるでしょうか？
hope to find out
分かることを願っています
if research can find it
研究でそれが発見できれば
protective antibodies
防御抗体
where is its antigen
その抗原はどこにありますか
That can be done like hepatitis B
B型肝炎のようにそれができる
Or something like a human milk-coated vaccine
あるいは人乳でコーティングされたワクチンのようなもの
can make a good vaccine
良いワクチンを作ることができる
This is the most ideal
これが一番理想的です
target antigen
標的抗原
And then after making it
そして作った後は
who
WHO
Like a baby or
赤ちゃんのように、あるいは
Which one is the student?
どっちが学生ですか？
Is it him or a girl or a boy
彼ですか、それとも女の子ですか、それとも男の子ですか
is his top priority
それは彼の最優先事項です
It is targeted for injection of vaccine
ワクチン注射の対象となる
that for existing
それは既存の
What about hepatitis B and human milk vaccines?
B型肝炎と母乳ワクチンについてはどうですか?
We're going to enhance its injection
インジェクションを強化していきます
vaccination rate
ワクチン接種率
Then we're going to work hard to overcome this
それでは、これを乗り越えるために頑張ります
Failed vaccination
ワクチン接種の失敗
situation, we're going to have to dig deeper into this whole vaccine
この状況では、このワクチン全体をさらに深く掘り下げる必要があるでしょう
How long can protect us, if possible
可能であればどれくらい私たちを守ってくれるでしょうか
Of course it is to make better vaccines, especially human reapplying vaccines
もちろん、より良いワクチン、特に人間に再適用するワクチンを作るためです。
This picture shows that in fact, it has been developing new
この写真は、実際に新しいものを開発していることを示しています。
Better vaccines, for example, this is the nine vaccines
より良いワクチン、たとえばこれは 9 つのワクチンです
It's not just this place, it's 16 and 18, it can cover everything
ここだけじゃない 16も18も全部カバーできる
At present, Taiwan also has a relatively large number of 52 and 58 types.
現在、台湾でも52型と58型が比較的多いです。
This kind of human catch-up vaccine
この種のヒトキャッチアップワクチン
So it is possible to add L2 and L1 together
したがって、L2とL1を一緒に追加することが可能です
These are new developments
これらは新たな展開です
so i think we'll just end here
だからここで終わりにしようと思う
That is to say, blocking the vaccine is not a dream
つまりワクチン阻止も夢ではない
I want to get in the way we have to start at an early age
幼い頃から始めなければならないのを邪魔したい
Here I would like to thank me for helping some of my colleagues
ここで、何人かの同僚を助けてくれたことに感謝したいと思います
And thank you all for being here today
そして、今日はここに来てくれてありがとう
Thank you all for joining our set of discussions
ディスカッションにご参加いただきありがとうございました
We are very grateful to Academician Zhang
張学術院士に非常に感謝しています
Professor Zhang gave us this wonderful speech
張先生が素晴らしい講演をしてくださいました
So we have about 20 minutes to 30 minutes now
それでは20分から30分ほどお時間をいただきます
Can Q&A
Q&Aができます
If you have a problem, please raise your hand
問題がある場合は手を挙げてください
Then press the green place here
次に、ここの緑色の場所を押します
Then introduce yourself briefly
それでは簡単に自己紹介を
ask more questions please
もっと質問してください
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
and very clear
そしてとても明確です
I work in a law firm
私は法律事務所で働いています
I often come here to give speeches occasionally when I have time.
私は時間があるときに時々ここに来てスピーチをします。
what i want to ask is
私が聞きたいのは
you just told us
あなたは今私たちに言いました
The United States has not yet tested for transplanted antigens
米国はまだ移植抗原の検査を行っていない
then also tell us
それなら私たちにも教えてください
japanese while they are watching mother
彼らは母親を見ている間日本人
It is only important to see that the surface antigen is positive
表面抗原が陽性であることだけが重要です
However, the last part of the data shows that
ただし、データの最後の部分は次のことを示しています。
Antigen transfer is actually super important
抗原移入は実際には非常に重要です
can you tell us
教えていただけますか
these two countries
この二つの国
their academics or their medical profession
彼らの学者や医療従事者
Why do you think you don't need to deal with inhibitors?
阻害剤に対処する必要がないのはなぜだと思いますか?
just ok
まあまあ
Thank you for this very good question
とても良い質問をありがとう
That is to say, the source of inhibitor is very important
つまり、阻害剤の供給源が非常に重要です
But what do they do in the United States?
しかし、彼らは米国で何をしているのでしょうか？
Because America they are rich
アメリカは金持ちだから
So they are making all mothers S-antigens
つまり、彼らはすべての母親をS抗原にしているのです
surface antigen
表面抗原
Then he gave him immunoglobulin
それから彼は免疫グロブリンを与えました
So he spends more money
それで彼はもっとお金を使う
What about the government of Taiwan?
台湾政府はどうですか？
He spent the money to test for inhibitors
彼は阻害剤の検査にお金を費やした
But he said that the negative source of inhibitor is actually better than
しかし、彼は、阻害剤のネガティブなソースは実際にはそれよりも優れていると述べました。
Inhibitors are more positive
阻害剤はよりポジティブです
He won't give him immune globulin
彼は免疫グロブリンを与えない
He just saves money on the immunoglobulin.
彼は免疫グロブリンの費用を節約するだけです。
Well, we are actually in the Ministry of Health and Welfare
さて、実は私たちは厚生省にいます。
CDC
CDC
Later there were some discussions
その後、いくつかの議論がありました
That is to say, we should learn
つまり、私たちは学ばなければならないのです
The US or we should maintain the status quo in Taiwan
米国か台湾の現状維持をすべきだ
Then our final conclusion is that
そして、私たちの最終的な結論は次のとおりです。
Because our research proves
私たちの研究が証明しているので、
Antigen negative mother
抗原陰性の母親
Actually only 0.14 to 0.29%
実際には 0.14 ～ 0.29% にすぎません
contagious to his children
彼の子供たちに伝染する
10% of the inhibitor positive
阻害剤陽性の 10%
Plus, if we're really going to treat these pregnant women in the future
さらに、将来的にこれらの妊婦を本当に治療するつもりなら、
If these pregnant women really want to take medicine
もしこの妊婦たちが本当に薬を飲みたいなら
We still need anti-inflammatory medicine
まだ抗炎症薬が必要です
It’s like going to the doctor’s anti-inflammation and then screening for high-level viruses
それは、医者に抗炎症薬を処方してもらってから、高レベルのウイルスを検査するようなものです
So the final decision is that we don't want to learn from the United States
したがって、最終的な決定は、米国から学びたくないということです。
Then we'll save the immunoglobulin money.
そうすれば免疫グロブリンのお金を節約できます。
Then go, but spend the money of the screening doctor and anti-inflammation
それから行きますが、スクリーニング医師と抗炎症剤のお金を使います
What about Japan? Japan has always
日本はどうでしょうか? 日本は常にそうしてきました。
They actually started vaccinations very early.
実際、彼らは非常に早くからワクチン接種を開始しました。
But in Japan they always feel that their hepatitis B
しかし日本では、彼らは常にB型肝炎に罹患していると感じています。
not they are not their most important problem
そうではない、彼らにとって最も重要な問題ではない
Most of them have hepatitis C
彼らのほとんどはC型肝炎に感染しています
Hepatitis C is more common in Japan
C型肝炎は日本でより一般的です
And they think it's the most important to hit these high-risk groups
そして彼らは、これらの高リスクグループを攻撃することが最も重要であると考えています
But their pediatrician
しかし、小児科医は、
And their hepatologist keeps telling me
肝臓専門医は私にこう言い続けています
they have been convincing the government
彼らは政府を説得してきた
Even the government has been making new vaccines
政府も新たなワクチンを開発中
But this part was finally convinced
でもこの部分はやっと納得できました
Now Japan is also starting to do this kind of depression for the whole people
今、日本もこの種の憂鬱を全国民に向けてやり始めている
So it means they still have approval
つまり、彼らはまだ承認を得ているということです
Does that one have a problem and wants to ask for leave?
その人は何か問題を抱えていて休暇を申請したいのですか？
come please
来てください
thank you for your very important question
非常に重要なご質問をありがとうございます
Hepatitis is ABCDE
肝炎はABCDEです
There are currently five
現在5つあります
Among them, Hepatitis A and Hepatitis E are Chrysostomy
このうち、A型肝炎とE型肝炎は喉頭瘻です。
Just eat something and pass it in
何かを食べてそれを渡すだけです
Chrysostom's is what we call fecal-oral infection
クリソストム病はいわゆる糞口感染症です
contaminated food
汚染された食品
and eat it in the stomach
そしてお腹の中で食べる
That's fecal-oral infection
それが糞口感染症です
BCDEs are bodily fluid and blood infections
BCDE は体液および血液の感染症です
So it's a dirty needle
つまり、それは汚れた針です
or blood or sexually transmitted
または血液または性感染症
Probably some contagious stunt like this
おそらくこのような伝染性のスタント
Okay, I don't know if there is any problem to ask for leave.
そうですね、休暇を申請することに問題があるかどうかはわかりません。
Professor Zhang made it very clear today
張教授は今日、こう明確に述べた。
Put the whole vaccination
ワクチンを全部入れてください
Cancer prevention is very in-depth and rolled out
がん予防は非常に綿密かつ展開されています
come here please
ここに来てください
ask now
今すぐ尋ねてください
Anti-cancer vaccine against Helicobacter eubacterium
ヘリコバクター・ユーバクテリウムに対する抗がんワクチン
how is the development
開発はどうですか
Helicobacter eubacterium
ヘリコバクター・ユーバクテリウム
In fact, many scholars want to make vaccines
実際、多くの学者がワクチンを作りたいと考えています
But the current development seems to be not going well
しかし、現在の開発はうまくいっていないようです
That is because maybe its really protective antigen
それは、おそらく本当に防御的な抗原だからです
Protective antibodies are actually not so clear
防御抗体は実際にはそれほど明確ではありません
But there are many studies
でも研究はたくさんある
In addition, because of its therapeutic drug
また、治療薬のため
was quite successful
かなり成功しました
So it seems that the current trend is to take medicine
ということで、最近は薬を飲むのが主流になっているようです。
to give medicine to those who have already got the infection
すでに感染している人に薬を与える
Of course we hope that one day there will be a good vaccine
もちろん、いつか良いワクチンが開発されることを願っています
Of course you say the whole virus will go down
もちろんあなたはウイルス全体が沈静化すると言います
Can the bacteria go down?
菌は減るのでしょうか？
At present, there seems to be no way to make an ideal vaccine
現時点では理想的なワクチンを作る方法はないようです
please
お願いします
ask the professor
教授に聞く
Just now you mentioned that
今、あなたはそれを言いましたね
Anyone under the age of 30 is vaccinated
30歳未満なら誰でも接種可能
Then do you recommend those over 30 years old who haven’t played before?
では、これまでプレイしたことがない30歳以上の人におすすめしますか？
Hurry up and get this vaccine now
急いでこのワクチンを今すぐ受けましょう
Thanks
ありがとう
That is to say, what we have seen from past research
つまり、これまでの研究から見えてきたことは、
Infection in Taiwan is actually
台湾での感染は実際に
From just now we see a line
先ほどから線が見えています
Just haven't had the vaccination yet
まだワクチン接種してないだけ
Flattened after two years of age
2歳を過ぎると平らになる
Said that the infection in Taiwan
台湾でも感染したとのこと
is the majority before the age of two
2歳までが大多数です
So it doesn't mean that it won't be contagious when you grow up
大人になったら感染しないわけではない
because
なぜなら
Because some steam heads were not clean in the past
過去に一部のスチームヘッドが汚れていたため
That's some clinic
それはどこかのクリニックです
He didn't have disinfection or dental check in the early days
彼は初期の頃、消毒もされず、歯も見えなかった
But now it's been very well disinfected.
でも今はしっかり消毒されています。
So what about people over 30?
では、30歳以上の人はどうでしょうか？
People over the age of 30 can go
30歳以上なら行ける
Test markers to see if you are negative for all three
マーカーをテストして、3 つすべてが陰性かどうかを確認します
If negative for surface antigen Negative for surface antibody
表面抗原陰性の場合 表面抗体陰性の場合
Then if the core antibody is negative, it is likely that you have not had it
コア抗体が陰性の場合は、コア抗体を持っていない可能性があります。
This kind of person is very rare, so this kind of person can be vaccinated
このような人は非常にまれなので、このような人にはワクチン接種が可能です
If the core antibody, the easiest way for us to screen with a marker is the core antibody
コア抗体の場合、マーカーを使用してスクリーニングする最も簡単な方法はコア抗体です
If the core antibody is positive, probably all will pass
コア抗体が陽性であればおそらく合格します。
come please
来てください
Professor, Professor, how does hepatitis turn into liver cancer?
先生、先生、肝炎はどうして肝臓がんになるのですか？
Great question, but a disaster
素晴らしい質問ですが、残念でした
Both are great questions. How does hepatitis turn into liver cancer?
どちらも素晴らしい質問ですが、肝炎はどのようにして肝臓がんに変化するのでしょうか?
We've all studied all our lives and are still finding the answers.
私たちは皆、人生を通じて研究してきましたが、まだ答えを見つけていません。
But in short it should be
しかし、要するにそうあるべきです
It is a trilogy of walking a bit like holding on to shoes
靴にしがみつくように歩く三部作です
That is to say it is hepatitis
つまり肝炎です
hepatitis then cirrhosis
肝炎、そして肝硬変
Then the liver comes and goes like this
すると肝臓はこうやって出たり入ったり
But it's not 100%, right?
でもそれは100％ではないですよね？
we just saw eighty percent
たった今80パーセントを見たところです
It seems to be going this way
このまま進んでいくようだ
In other words, inflammation first
つまり、まず炎症が起こる
Then after inflammation, cell necrosis
そして炎症が起こった後、細胞が壊死してしまいます。
After necrosis, cells want to regenerate
壊死した後、細胞は再生しようとします
because we have some tissue damage
組織に損傷があるため
For example, we have wounds on our bodies
たとえば、私たちの体には傷があります。
we just want to regenerate it
私たちはそれを再生成したいだけです
Then our body already has a regeneration mechanism
つまり、私たちの体にはすでに再生機構が備わっているのです。
But when it needs to regenerate in the liver?
しかし、肝臓でいつ再生する必要があるのでしょうか?
will launch the wrong message
間違ったメッセージが表示されます
That is to say, some of what we call liver cells
つまり、私たちが肝細胞と呼ぶものの一部です。
there are some cells it's coming out
いくつかの細胞が出てきています
When the injury is too serious
怪我が重すぎる場合
activates liver cells
肝細胞を活性化する
there are some cells it regenerates excessively
過剰に再生する細胞がいくつかあります
becomes a carcinogenic phenomenon
発がん性現象になる
it doesn't know when to stop
いつ止まるかわからない
just keep walking
ただ歩き続けてください
that becomes a condition like cancer
それは癌のような状態になる
So the current theory is that
したがって、現在の理論は次のとおりです
inflamed
炎症を起こした
then hurt
それから傷つきます
and then regenerate after possible damage
損傷の可能性がある場合は再生します
Then something wrong happened with regeneration
その後、再生時に問題が発生しました
Rebirth should be just after birth
生まれ変わるのは誕生直後であるべきだ
about to stop
停止しようとしています
The result is non-stop life can not stop
その結果、止まらないノンストップライフが生まれる
become albinism
白皮症になる
just keep growing
ただ成長し続ける
ok come here
わかった、ここに来て
Then wait a moment for the classmate in black at the back
それでは、後ろにいる黒服のクラスメイトを待ってください
Come
来て
Changjiang is smart
長江は賢い
i want to ask a question
私は質問をしたいです
It is written on the slide behind you just now
先ほど後ろのスライドに書いてあります
speak mother's words
母の言葉を話す
inhibitor antigen or s antigen
インヒビター抗原または s 抗原
that very high words
とても高尚な言葉
That vaccination is prone to failure
ワクチン接種は失敗しやすい
that's probably because
それはおそらく
That is, the mother already has
つまり母親はすでに持っている
Antibodies against anti-antigen and s-antigen
抗抗原およびS抗原に対する抗体
Then to synthesize the subsequent vaccines
その後、後続のワクチンを合成します
Because your vaccine came from the s antigen after all
結局のところ、あなたのワクチンは s 抗原から作られたものだからです
yes this is
はい、これです
mothers with s antigen positive
S抗原陽性の母親
she would not have
彼女はそうしなかったでしょう
Measured Not absolute
測定されたもの 絶対的なものではない
But most of them are undetectable antibody S antibody
しかし、そのほとんどは検出不可能な抗体であるS抗体です
How should I put it, in fact, if you understand our clinical laboratory
実際、私たちの臨床検査室を理解していただければ、何と言えばいいでしょうか。
doing antigen-antibody reaction
抗原抗体反応をしている
You'll find out that it actually has a cut value
実際にカット値があることがわかります
That is to say, I measured out a bunch of values
つまり、たくさんの値を測定しました
But this line, after drawing a line
でもこの線、線を引いたあと
Above this line is called positive
この線より上を陽性といいます
Below this line is called negative
この線より下はネガティブと呼ばれます
This is the positive control group after many tests
これは多くのテストを経たポジティブコントロールグループです
This negative control group is the last test to be tested
この陰性対照グループは最後に検査される検査です
If you had a test you would know
検査を受ければわかるだろう
It's actually a very artificial personality.
それは実際には非常に人工的な人格です。
Then say this is positive and this is negative
次に、これはポジティブで、これはネガティブだと言います
Then this S antigen-positive mother has a lot of S antigens
そうすると、このS抗原陽性の母親はS抗原をたくさん持っています。
So almost when you have S antigen all over your body
つまり、S抗原が体中にあるときとほぼ同じです。
His body may produce a little S antibody, and he will be poisoned immediately
彼の体は少量のS抗体を生成する可能性があり、すぐに中毒になります。
So there's never a way in your blood
だからあなたの血には決して道はない
S antibodies are almost always undetectable
S 抗体はほとんどの場合検出されません
but there is a force
しかし力はあります
In addition, the mutant strain of S just mentioned
また、先ほど述べたSの変異株
People with S mutants sometimes still have antibodies and antigens at the same time
S 変異を持つ人は、抗体と抗原を同時に持っていることがあります
That's its antigen, that's the mutant
それがその抗原、それが変異体です
Its antibody is an antibody against the wild strain
その抗体は野生株に対する抗体です
two different antibodies
2 つの異なる抗体
This is too complicated so let's not talk about it
これは複雑すぎるので話さないようにしましょう
The other one is E antigen and E antibody
もう一つはE抗原とE抗体です
You also mentioned the E antigen
E抗原についても言及しましたね
E antigen E antibody we often say when we look at patient information
患者情報を見るときによく言われる E 抗原 E 抗体
Why is this person positive for E antigen? Positive? Positive. One day the E antigen will disappear.
なぜこの人は E 抗原陽性なのですか? 陽性ですか? 陽性です。いつか E 抗原は消えます。
But he didn't develop antibodies
しかし抗体はできなかった
Then finally one day he developed antibodies
そしてついにある日、彼は抗体を開発しました
Or this guy is E antigen positive Positive Positive
それともこの人はE抗原陽性 陽性 陽性
When the result is positive
結果が陽性の場合
It's strange that his antibody is also positive
抗体も陽性なのが不思議だ
It becomes E antigen positive and positive at the same time
E抗原陽性と陽性が同時になる
E antigen negative and negative presence
E抗原陰性および陰性の存在
This is a transitional period
今は過渡期です
he won't be like this forever
彼は永遠にこのままではない
It means that when the E antigen of this person is gradually decreasing
この人のE抗原が徐々に減っていくと
He may have the ability to have antibodies that surpass him
彼は自分を超える抗体を持つ能力を持っているかもしれない
So he was withdrawn to
それで彼は引きこもりました
But this situation is two fighting
しかし、この状況は二者の戦いです
Is it the virus that wins or the human race?
勝つのはウイルスか人類か?
Wait until the day when humans win
人類が勝つ日まで待ってください
He suppressed the antibody and came out
抗体を抑えて出てきた
Antibodies are gone forever
抗体は永久に失われます
But in this inhibitor positive mother
しかし、この阻害剤陽性の母親では
The comparison between positive and negative inhibitory elements will change
ポジティブな抑制要素とネガティブな抑制要素の比較が変化する
some pregnant women
一部の妊婦
He was anti-antibody positive in the previous life of the production
本番の前世では抗抗体陽性だった
Postpartum he cleared some of the virus
出産後、彼はウイルスの一部を除去しました
So he later had a postpartum
それで彼はその後産後を迎えました
Due to hormonal changes
ホルモンの変化により
inhibitory antibody
阻害抗体
But it shouldn't be in the scope of our discussion today
しかし、それは今日の議論の範囲に入るべきではありません
Because we're talking about this pregnancy period
なぜなら、私たちはこの妊娠期間について話しているからです
this contagious condition
この伝染病の状態
Thanks
ありがとう
There is another classmate here who wears a substitute
ここには替えの服を着ている別のクラスメートがいます
Then I'm half a high school student now
そうするともう半分は高校生ですね
There are stories that have been learned before
以前に学んだ話があります
Inger had that kind of AFA in her pregnancy
インガーは妊娠中にそのようなAFAを患っていました
He has some preexisting genetic disease or certain mutations that could be linked
彼はいくつかの既存の遺伝病または関連する可能性のある特定の突然変異を持っています
I don’t know if there will be some connection with the high amount of genetic antigen and S antigen in the mother’s body
母体内の遺伝性抗原やS抗原の多さと関係があるかどうかはわかりません
Could that be why one of the injections failed?
それが、注射の 1 つが失敗した理由でしょうか?
He knows that this fetal protein is very hard work
彼はこの胎児たんぱく質が非常に大変な仕事であることを知っています
In fact, it is a coincidence that fetal protein is the marker of human liver cancer
実際、胎児タンパク質がヒト肝臓がんのマーカーであるのは偶然です。
It means that I just mentioned how this cancer can be detected
つまり、このがんがどのように検出されるかを先ほど述べたということです
How can fetal protein be detected in liver cancer
肝がんにおける胎児タンパク質はどのようにして検出されるのでしょうか
Fetal protein should be present in the fetus
胎児タンパク質は胎児に存在する必要があります
Then after birth for 12 months he will slowly decline
その後、生後12か月でゆっくりと衰退していきます
We've done research with our children in the past
私たちは過去に子供たちと一緒に研究をしたことがあります
We have to measure the rate of decline of fetal protein
胎児たんぱく質の減少速度を測定する必要がある
Found to about 12 months
発見から約12か月
Fetal protein returns to normal
胎児たんぱく質が正常に戻る
The normal value is about 10
正常値は10程度
It used to be Chedai 20 Narogram per amyl
以前はChedai 20 Narogram per amylでした
blood that can be thinned
薄めることができる血液
Now it is cut to 10 Narogram per amyl
現在はアミルあたり 10 ナグラムに削減されています
It means that when the fetus is 12 months old, there will be a very high amount from the fetus
これは、胎児が生後12か月になると、胎児から非常に多くの量が分泌されることを意味します。
Fetal protein is very high at birth
出生時の胎児たんぱく質は非常に高い
higher in utero
子宮内のより高い位置にある
It represents these stem cells
これらの幹細胞を表します
In fact, these stem cells that produce fetal protein
実際、胎児タンパク質を生成するこれらの幹細胞は、
It was actually very tall in the mother's womb
実は母親の胎内ではとても背が高かったのです
very vigorous
非常に活発な
These hepatoblasts actually have many conditions
これらの肝芽細胞には実際には多くの条件があります
But it is born in the baby's 12 months
でも赤ちゃんは生後12ヶ月で生まれます
All have been declining during the first year
初年度はいずれも減少傾向にある
so it shouldn't be high
だから高くないはずだ
So if an adult suddenly detects high levels of fetal protein
したがって、成人が突然高レベルの胎児性タンパク質を検出した場合、
I said, do you have liver cancer?
私は言いました、あなたは肝臓がんですか？
That's why it's called a marker for liver cancer screening.
そのため、肝臓がん検診のマーカーと呼ばれています。
just asked a very important question
とても重要な質問をしました
Then what you mentioned just now is about the fetal protein
それから、今おっしゃったのは胎児性たんぱく質のことです。
Rising with this mom this brooder
この母親と一緒に立ち上がります、この陰気な人
Is it related to the failure of the injection in the fetal area?
胎児領域への注射の失敗と関係があるのでしょうか？
In fact, we have never studied such a project
実際、私たちはそのようなプロジェクトを研究したことがありません
there is no way to say
言う方法はありません
what kind of relationship will there be between them
彼らの間にはどのような関係があるだろうか
because it is essentially
それは本質的にそうだから
Mother because of the placenta of our human mothers
人間の母親の胎盤のおかげで母親になる
Yes should be a very good barrier
はい、非常に優れた障壁になるはずです
After all, the liver virus passed
結局肝臓ウイルスは通過した
unless the placenta has a hole
胎盤に穴が開いていなければ
That course our para-obstetrician studies
そのコースは私たちの準産科医の研究です
Sometimes the placenta has holes
胎盤に穴が開いている場合もあります
go to it
そこに行く
It's called the feeling of the womb
それは子宮の感覚と呼ばれるものです
So currently I have no way to figure out
したがって、現時点ではそれを把握する方法がありません
When fetal protein is in the baby's womb
胎児性たんぱく質が赤ちゃんの子宮内にあるとき
what would it have to do with this
それと何の関係があるだろうか
here is another problem
ここに別の問題があります
then behind
それから後ろに
that is, if the parents have that
つまり、両親がそれを持っている場合
the one with chronic hepatitis
慢性肝炎のある方
words of hepatitis
肝炎の言葉
It is easy to destroy the liver liver to children
子供の肝臓は破壊されやすい
Then can we do that pre-marital health check?
では、結婚前健康診断はできるのでしょうか？
Go find out if that parent is one of them has chronic hepatitis Advocate
その親に慢性肝炎患者がいるかどうか調べに行く
avoid having small children if at all
小さな子供がいる場合は避けてください
as a pediatrician
小児科医として
Of course I don't want people not to have children.
もちろん、私は人々に子供を持たないことを望んでいません。
Otherwise we would have no patients to see
そうでなければ診てもらえる患者がいなくなってしまう
In fact, it's more important not for us small doctors
実際のところ、私たち小規模の医師にとってより重要なことはありません。
Actually for our country
実は我が国にとって
The people are the masters of the country
人民こそが国の主人である
So we have been promoting everyone to have more children
そこで私たちは皆にもっと子供を産むよう奨励してきました
It's best to have four or five, or even ten.
4 つか 5 つ、あるいは 10 つあるのがベストです。
So it's definitely not a reason not to have children
だからそれは子供を産まない理由には絶対にならない
And that means there is a way, it can be prevented by vaccines
つまり、ワクチンで予防できる方法があるということです
Even if we block in the future
今後ブロックしても
Premarital checkup is of course very good
婚前診断はもちろん良いです
That is to say, pre-marital examination
つまり、結婚前検査です。
We now have some young parents who are already doing pre-marital checkups
現在、すでに結婚前検査を受けている若い親もいます。
We know mothers are actually the biggest
私たちは母親が実際に一番大きいことを知っています
Is the father infected?
父親も感染してるの？
There are also father-son infections, but there are more
父子感染もありますが、それ以上の感染があります。
mother is the most important
母親が一番大切です
the mother or father to infect
母親または父親が感染させる
Actually there is another
実はもう一つあるんです
we do wedding checks
私たちは結婚調査をします
there is another meaning
別の意味があります
Just don't want husband and wife to infect each other
夫婦がお互いに感染しないようにしたいだけ
So if a couple
それでカップルなら
like boyfriend and girlfriend
彼氏と彼女のように
If they go for a check-up before they get married
結婚前に健康診断に行ったら
the side the side that doesn't
そうでない側
Should get vaccinated
予防接種を受けるべき
This should be
これはそうあるべきです
This is to prevent husband and wife from infecting each other
夫婦間での感染を防ぐためです
It is more important to prevent couples
カップルを防ぐことがより重要です
Then go on, of course, just watch
それから続けて、もちろん見てください
Can the mother infect the child?
母親が子供に感染させる可能性はあるのでしょうか？
this is another
これは別のものです
We also don't want couples to infect each other
また、カップルが互いに感染することも望んでいません。
but have to have a baby
でも赤ちゃんを産まなければならない
ok this side
はい、こちら側です
lady please
女性、お願いします
about the treatment of the pregnant woman
妊婦の治療について
this part of hepatitis
肝炎のこの部分
Because the professor just mentioned
先ほど教授がおっしゃったので、
then i want to ask
それから聞きたいです
if during pregnancy
妊娠中の場合
taking medicine
薬を飲んでいる
Will it affect the development of the fetus?
胎児の発育に影響はありますか？
This is the first question
これが最初の質問です
The second question is
2番目の質問は、
You have written 28 weeks above
上で 28 週間と書きました
what is the consideration
考慮事項は何ですか
Thanks
ありがとう
In fact, this is a very, very important question
実際、これは非常に重要な質問です
that's what we do
それが私たちがやっていることです
When I started designing this clinical trial
この臨床試験の設計を始めたとき
In fact, we all get nervous when doing clinical trials.
実際、臨床試験を行うときは誰でも緊張します。
just in case
念のため
what i did with this pregnant woman
私がこの妊婦に何をしたのか
What kind of side effects did it really have?
実際にはどのような副作用があったのでしょうか？
I'd feel bad conscience
良心の呵責を感じるだろう
If trying to save him ends up hindering him, wouldn't that be bad?
救おうとして邪魔になるなら、それはダメじゃないですか？
So we have to refer to AIDS research
したがって、エイズの研究を参照する必要があります。
AIDS, because they are ahead of us, they have done a lot of treatment for pregnant women
エイズは私たちよりも先を行っているため、妊婦に対して多くの治療を行ってきました。
So we went to see because this drug happens to be a drug that can be used for AIDS
たまたまこの薬がエイズに使える薬だったので見に行きました
So there are some
それで、いくつかあります
It is the login of the congenital model
先天性モデルのログインです
Then find their login details found
次に、ログインの詳細が見つかったことを確認します
actually
実際
Congenital models did not increase at all
先天性モデルはまったく増加しなかった
and
と
The base value is as much so we just
基本値は同じなので、
dare to go down and do it
あえて下がってやってみよう
This is the first reason
これが最初の理由です
The second is to say this 28 weeks
2つ目は、これを28週間と言うことです
you are very careful noticing
あなたはとても注意深く気づいています
This 28 week thing is very, very good
この28週間のことはとてもとても良いです
That is to say, 28 weeks
つまり28週間
Mainly because of fear
主に恐怖のせいで
That is to say, at the time of the third generation
つまり3代目の時点では
We think the fetus is already formed
胎児はすでに形成されていると考えられます
So in case there is any deformity
なので、万が一変形があった場合には
I won't be blamed by my parents
親に責められることはないよ
Although in fact we know very well
実際のところ、私たちはよく知っていますが、
it's not because of this to cause
これが原因ではない
But it's hard for you to tell your parents
でも親には言いにくいですよね
Is this going to
これはそうなるのですか
it still blames you for saying maybe
もしかしたらと言ったことをまだあなたを責めている
So 28 weeks has it's benefits which is to say
つまり、28週間には利点があるということです
I told him
私は彼に言った
You can see the shapes born in the early stage
初期段階で生まれた形がわかります
So 28 weeks is pretty safe
つまり、28週間はかなり安全です
So on the one hand it is the tertiary
それで、一方ではそれは三次です
In fact, there are some predecessors
実は前任者もいる
drugs have been done
麻薬が行われた
So we think there is no problem
ですので問題ないと考えております
So of course this medicine is useful?
では、この薬はもちろん役に立ちますか？
Because it is pregnant there are ABCD categories
妊娠中なのでABCDカテゴリーがあります
In the past, some people used a series of medicines
過去には、一連の薬を使用する人もいました
did a little experiment
ちょっとした実験をしました
Looks like it works too
それも機能するようです
Then the drug we chose is category B.
そこで私たちが選んだ薬剤はカテゴリーBです。
Of course it is safer than class C
もちろんクラスCよりも安全です
Type A vitamins
A型ビタミン
Pregnant women in this category can eat
このカテゴリーの妊婦は食べられます
So it should be safe
だから安全なはずだよ
Come on, there's a problem later
さあ、後で問題が発生します
I don't want to ask Professor Zhang a question
張教授には質問したくない
That is, after listening to the speech just now
つまり、今のスピーチを聞いて、
It seems that hepatitis B and C are the cause of hepatitis
肝炎の原因はB型肝炎とC型肝炎だそうです
The main reason
最主要原因
Is that someone who doesn't have any hepatitis?
その人は肝炎にかかっていない人ですか？
won't get liver cancer
肝臓がんにならない
it's also a good
それも良いです
Scholars around the world are currently studying
世界中の学者が現在研究中です
The answer is of course no
答えはもちろんノーです
That is to say, if we take the world's
つまり、世界のことを考えてみると、
B liver is taken away
B 肝都弄走
Do humans not have liver cancer?
人間には肝臓がんはないのでしょうか？
The answer is of course no
答えはもちろんノーです
there will still be
まだあるでしょう
but it will be less
でも減るだろう
will be much less
はるかに少なくなります
Because liver B occupies a large part
肝臓Bが多くを占めているため
that's us
それが私たちです
For example, our children
たとえば、私たちの子供たち
there is another liver
もう一つ肝臓があります
Liver model
肝臓モデル
stem cells
乾母細胞
Stem blasts are similar to liver cancer
幹芽細胞は肝臓がんに似ています
it is an innate stem cell
それは自然幹細胞です
embryonic cell cancer
胚細胞がん
then becomes
となる
that's another
それは別です
sometimes it gets to the teens
時々それは十代の若者たちに及ぶ
But adults don't have this disease
しかし、大人にはこの病気はありません
Adults don't have this disease
大人にはこの病気はありません
but adults it will have some fat
でも大人だと脂肪がつきます
lesion
病変
some western countries
いくつかの西側諸国
They have less liver B or C
彼らは肝臓BまたはCが少ない
But they still have liver cancer
しかし彼らはまだ肝臓がんを患っている
We call non-non-B type
非非B型といいます。
this liver cancer
この肝臓がんは
but much less
しかし、はるかに少ない
Hello, little professor, I am
こんにちは、小さな教授、私は
Chen Jianmin
チェン・ジェンミン
I appreciate your great speech
素晴らしいスピーチに感謝します
I have a question
質問があります
If it is a vaccine for the general public to avoid liver
一般の人が肝臓を避けるためのワクチンであれば
Prevented 90% of childhood infections
小児の感染症の90%を予防
Then
それから
that is
あれは
Hepatocellular carcinoma in children
小児の肝細胞がん
finally possible
ようやく可能になりました
The above are caused by infection
上記は感染によって引き起こされます
Then why is it that the whole people can't beat the email?
では、なぜ国民全員がメールに勝てないのでしょうか？
It is reduced to 90%, reduced to 70%
90%に減ります、70%に減ります
That's a great question, that's what I keep asking myself
素晴らしい質問ですね、それが私が自分自身に問い続けていることです
Question Asked I've been asking this question myself
尋ねられた質問 私自身もこの質問をしてきました
your question is very good
あなたの質問はとても良いです
We often talk about the 90% and 70%
私たちはよく 90% と 70% について話します。
In fact, I deliberately wrote 90% and 70% for everyone to see.
実は、皆さんに見ていただくために、あえて90％、70％と書きました。
90% and 70% are 20% different
90%と70%は20%違う
How did the 20% come about?
20％というのはどうやって生まれたのでしょうか？
Why can't he become
なぜ彼はなれないのか
There is nothing you can do to prevent this
これを防ぐためにできることは何もありません
so we were thinking
それで私たちは考えていました
These 10% of people are the people who failed the vaccination
この10％の人たちはワクチン接種に失敗した人たちです
My hypothesis is that
私の仮説はそれです
These people develop infections at a higher rate than others
これらの人々は他の人々よりも高い率で感染症を発症します
Why because he failed his vaccination
なぜ予防接種に失敗したのか
Indicates that his mother's virus is very high
母親のウイルス感染力が非常に高いことを示している
so his mom gave him the worst virus
だから彼の母親は彼に最悪のウイルスを与えた
lots of viruses
たくさんのウイルス
It is likely that his entire liver disease process
おそらく彼の肝疾患の全過程が
is more serious
より深刻です
We probably can't do it right now
おそらく今はそれができない
really to prove him
本当に彼を証明するために
I can probably do it now
たぶん今でもできるよ
Which means I'm going to track down these kids.
つまり、私はこの子供たちを追跡するつもりです。
Then I was watching his virus
それから私は彼のウイルスを観察していました
I'm working on his natural virus right now
私は今彼の自然ウイルスの研究をしています
Is it more serious
もっと深刻ですか
then his whole this
それから彼のこれ全部
Currently we have a little preliminary
現在、少し予備的なものがあります
The result is probably to see these
その結果、おそらくこれらが表示されるでしょう
after vaccination
ワクチン接種後
failed kid
失敗した子供
as if his whole
まるで彼の全体のように
The course of the disease will be prolonged
病気の経過は長引くだろう
Compare
比較
The whole course will be longer
コース全体が長くなります
Then the period of immunity will be longer
そうなると免疫の期間も長くなる
everyone see here
みんなここ見てるよ
I don't have a way to fully answer this question yet
この質問に完全に答える方法はまだありません
But thank you for the question
でも質問してくれてありがとう
actually a very
実際には非常に
I think college students can ask questions like
大学生は次のような質問をすることができると思います
I admire it very much
とても感心します
I probably didn't when I was in college
大学時代は無かったかも
incapable of asking such questions
そのような質問をすることができない
sir please
先生、お願いします
i want to ask two questions
2つの質問がしたいです
The first is to often hear people say
1つ目は、人々がこう言うのをよく聞くことです。
in everyone's body
みんなの体の中に
have cancer cells
がん細胞がある
right this time
今度こそ
How does the second cancer cell arise
2番目のがん細胞はどのようにして発生するのか
This is also a big question
これも大きな疑問です
possible
可能
I think it's possible to reach a certain age
ある程度の年齢になると可能だと思います
Yes, there are really cancer cells in the body
はい、体内には本当に癌細胞が存在します
I believe
私は信じている
but this
しかしこれは
this has very good questions
これはとても良い質問です
So it takes a lot of scientists
したがって、多くの科学者が必要です
Let's answer this question together
この質問に一緒に答えましょう
But our body has a very good immune system
しかし、私たちの体には非常に優れた免疫システムが備わっています
it can put that
それはそれを置くことができます
If you just had these bad cells
もしこれらの悪い細胞を持っていたら
you just put it
あなたはそれを置いただけです
let it shrink
縮めてみましょう
let it die
死なせてください
so what
だから何
it won't keep reproducing
再生産し続けることはない
So this is one that our human body inherently has
つまり、これは私たち人間の体が本来持っているものです
Protect our own muscle mass
自分自身の筋肉量を守る
so this is a
これは
human body
人体
nice this
いいですね、これ
A natural immune system against cancer
がんに対する自然免疫システム
come kill it
殺しに来てください
it naturally stops growing
自然に成長が止まる
But if you provide
しかし、あなたが提供した場合、
very good microenvironment
非常に良い微環境
let it be in this microenvironment
この微小環境に任せてください
have a good immune system
良好な免疫システムを持っている
support its continued growth
継続的な成長をサポートする
good bleeding
良い出血
let it grow
成長させてください
Then this cancer will gradually change from a cell to a cluster
その後、このがんは細胞からクラスターへと徐々に変化します。
A group becomes 0.5 cm
1グループが0.5cmになります
Then just 1 cm
あとは1センチだけ
growing up
育つ
Then it produces a lot of blood vessels
すると、たくさんの血管が生成されます
Then I kept growing up
それから私は成長し続けました
become an itchy and fatter
かゆみが増して太る
The condition that gets more and more itchy
どんどんかゆみが増していく状態
beat us
私たちを倒します
good
良い
Come
来て
this classmate
このクラスメート
Then come see this gentleman again
それからまたこの紳士に会いに来てください
Hello Professor Zhang
こんにちは、張教授
I'm Xu Yujia
私は徐裕佳です
Then I would like to ask about
それからお聞きしたいのですが、
Because the professor just mentioned that
先ほど教授がおっしゃったので、
Nasal and liver vaccines are mainly
鼻ワクチンと肝臓ワクチンは主に
Antigens enter the body
抗原が体内に侵入する
The body then produces antibodies
その後、体は抗体を生成します
or part of an immunoglobulin
または免疫グロブリンの一部
That's more to do with the immune system
それはむしろ免疫系と関係がある
that's for rhinovirus
それはライノウイルス用です
That's the way it infects parts
そうやって部品に感染するんだよ
Is there any relevant research on
関連する研究はありますか
Studies have shown that if infected
研究によると、感染した場合、
and then cause some
そして、いくつかの原因を引き起こす
eventually cause cancer cells to proliferate
最終的にはがん細胞を増殖させます
did that
それをしました
just use some drugs
いくつかの薬を使用するだけです
or give it some cellular signals
または携帯信号を与えてください
let it achieve cell shedding or something
細胞脱落か何かを達成させてください
Prevent the spread or proliferation of cancer
がんの広がりや増殖を防ぐ
Is there any research on this
これに関する研究はありますか
Thanks
ありがとう
Yes, yes, it is the cure for cancer
はい、はい、それは癌の治療法です
It's called cancer treatment
いわゆるガン治療です
or cancer treatment
またはがん治療
In fact, vaccines include anti-cancer vaccines and therapeutic vaccines
実際、ワクチンには抗がんワクチンと治療ワクチンが含まれます。
and cancer drugs
そして抗がん剤
Then what you just mentioned is actually
それから、あなたが今言ったことは、実は
currently exists
現在存在します
There is a licensed
ライセンスがある
There is a drug that treats stem cancer
幹がんを治療する薬がある
Then it is a cell that allows
次に、それを可能にする細胞です
effective people it will let the cell blast net
効果的な人々は細胞をネットに爆発させるでしょう
then zoom out
次にズームアウトします
What a pity
お気の毒に
Its effects are not yet broadly
その影響はまだ広範囲には及んでいない
That's pretty limited
それはかなり限定的です
but already exists
しかしすでに存在します
So current scientists are studying
そこで現在の科学者たちは研究を行っています
like you said
あなたが言ったように
better better medicine
より良いより良い薬
to treat this cancer
このがんを治療するために
Well, this level of it is of course treatment-oriented.
まあ、この程度のことは当然治療目的です。
this bus
このバス
A served Mr. and then in the back
Aさんが氏に仕え、その後奥で
right
右
just mentioned symptoms
先ほど述べた症状
In fact, the media often tells us that
実際、メディアはよく次のように伝えます。
Professor Xu Jinshan
許晋山教授
his sister
妹
The liver is a silent organ
肝臓は沈黙の臓器です
so often
しばしば
Liver disease is asymptomatic
肝臓病は無症状です
In fact, everyone already has this concept
実はこの概念は誰もがすでに持っています
Liver really can't speak
肝臓は本当に話すことができません
really no symptoms
本当に症状がない
there is
がある
you mentioned itching
あなたはかゆみについて言いました
or
また
Some people have jaundice
黄疸が出る人もいる
yellow bile
黄色の胆汁
allergy
過敏
This liver may not necessarily be directly related to liver disease.
この肝臓は必ずしも肝疾患に直接関係しているわけではありません。
that but
それはしかし
If you have this jaundice
この黄疸がある場合
That's one of the signs of liver disease
それは肝臓病の兆候の一つです
There is still itching, part of it is not an allergy
かゆみはまだありますが、一部はアレルギーではありません
cholestasis
胆汁うっ滞
When this liver cancer blocks the bile duct
この肝臓がんが胆管を閉塞すると、
Or when the patient becomes violent
あるいは患者が暴力的になったとき
or severe hepatitis
または重度の肝炎
it will turn yellow
黄色になります
Then its bile will stagnate
そうなると胆汁は停滞してしまいます
It may also itch at that time
その時も痒くなるかも知れません
or be very tired
またはとても疲れている
If it's just an itchy skin allergy
単なる皮膚のかゆみアレルギーの場合
It shouldn't have much to do with this.
これとはあまり関係がないはずです。
I just said that eating green onions and parsley is easier to get dry A
ネギやパセリを食べるとパサつきやすいと先ほど言いましたA
Yes, as Vice President Chen said
はい、陳副総統が言ったように
not washed
洗っていない
Ordinary people say this
普通の人はこう言うよ
Because when we eat green onions and coriander
ネギとパクチーを食べると
Many of them are washed and eaten raw.
多くは洗って生で食べられます。
Then if in the process of cultivation like this
では、このように修煉の過程にある場合、
When you are contaminated with hepatitis A virus
A型肝炎ウイルスに汚染されている場合
may be infected
感染している可能性があります
There are also such cases abroad
海外でもそういう例はある
Then if you eat raw corpses
生の死体を食べると
It is important to wash vegetables when
野菜を洗うときは洗うことが大切です
If you say your green onions and cilantro are cooked
ネギとコリアンダーが調理できたと言ったら
just put it in for a while
しばらく入れておいてください
That way there's less chance of getting an infection.
そうすれば感染する可能性は低くなります。
Raw food is more
生の食べ物はもっと
It was also found in Germany a while ago
少し前にドイツでも発見されました
when eating lettuce
レタスを食べるとき
Lettuce Salads Get Infected When They Are Not Washed
レタスサラダは洗わないと感染する
There are many such sleepers in the United States
アメリカにはそのような寝台車がたくさんあります
This is oral infection
これは経口感染症です
The classmate in red at the back still has his picture
後ろの赤い服を着たクラスメイトはまだ写真を持っています
The classmate in the red dress first
まずは赤いドレスを着たクラスメイト
hello teacher i want to ask two questions
こんにちは、先生、二つ質問したいのですが
The first question is about
最初の質問は、
I just mentioned that there are about three layers of Tumor in HCC
HCC には約 3 層の腫瘍があると先ほど述べました。
The pronucleus with HBV DNA looks like this
HBV DNAを持つ前核はこんな感じ
Compared to HBV it is 99.7%
HBVと比較すると99.7%
Then I want to ask what is the reason for the difference in the middle like this
では、このように真ん中が違うのはなぜなのか聞きたいです。
You're talking about DNA pre-entry
DNAの事前入力について話しているのですね
Yes, dragged into the tissue that made it cancerous
はい、組織に引き込まれて癌化しました
part of the DNA b hepatovirus inserts
DNA b ヘパトウイルスインサートの一部
30% of the population, but 90% of HPV
人口の30％、しかしHPVの90％
About seventy percent, three-sixty-sevenths
約70パーセント、67分の3
then answer this question first
それなら最初にこの質問に答えてください
That is to say, after all, viral genes are involved in cancer.
つまり、結局のところ、ウイルス遺伝子ががんに関与しているということです。
Is it directly related to the occurrence of cancer?
それは癌の発生に直接関係しているのでしょうか？
Scholars probably have some arguments
学者にはおそらくいくつかの議論があるでしょう
That is to say, the DNA is pulled into this place
つまりここにDNAが引き込まれているのです
Which gene is involved in human beings?
人間にはどの遺伝子が関係しているのでしょうか?
as if we are currently
あたかも私たちが現在にいるかのように
We've been working on one for years
私たちは何年もかけてその開発に取り組んできました
one gene on one skewed body
1 つの歪んだ体に 1 つの遺伝子
The gene called RBNY
RBNYという遺伝子
It just happened to be from our little friend
それはたまたま私たちの小さな友達からのものだった
His liver cancer tissue and then
彼の肝臓がん組織とその後
After the DNA is pulled in, we go to study
DNAが取り込まれたら、研究に行きます
the neighbor next to it
その隣の隣人
what is this gene
この遺伝子は何ですか
But what about people from all over the world
しかし、世界中の人々はどうでしょうか
research looks up
研究が調べる
drawn in human
人間で描かれた
Lung genetics are not fixed
肺の遺伝学は固定されていない
It often has pull-ins in different positions
さまざまな位置にプルインがあることがよくあります
So there's a cancer relationship between the two
つまり、この二人の間には癌の関係があるということです
not very sure
よくわからない
But maybe part of it is related
でも部分的には関係あるのかもしれない
Because its ratio is higher
比率が高いので
Then its precancerous lesions are relatively low
前がん病変は比較的少ない
But it's already started to get involved
でももう絡み始めてるよ
because it has reverse
逆があるから
It can be involved in such AIDS treatment
このようなエイズ治療にも携わることができます
that really early days
本当に初期の頃
It's not that badly infected
そこまでひどい感染症ではない
The damage is not that bad
ダメージはそこまでひどくない
it's 0%
それは0%です
So I guess my answer is just this
だから私の答えはこれだけだと思います
doesn't fully answer your question
あなたの質問に完全には答えていません
you may be partially answering
部分的に答えているかもしれません
come on next classmate please
さあ、次のクラスメートをお願いします
i think one last question
最後にもう一つ質問があると思います
Thanks for the time
お時間をいただきありがとうございました
Now everyone has a great talk
今、みんながとても楽しい話をしています
Today's content is mainly aimed at preventive cancer
今日の内容は主にがんの予防を目的としています
section on preventive vaccines
予防ワクチンに関するセクション
in the content of the speech
スピーチの内容で
Actually I mentioned
実は私も言いました
Human such as poisonous virus and liver itching
人間の有毒ウイルスや肝臓のかゆみなど
Viruses may sneak into human DNA
ウイルスは人間のDNAに侵入する可能性がある
the closest part of the womb
子宮の最も近い部分
Sometimes even see the human virus
時には人間のウイルスも見える
The part of 1617 will be shown
1617の部分が表示されます
Then according to my previous knowledge
それから私の以前の知識によると
There are some research groups that try to treat these manifestations as
これらの症状を次のように扱おうとする研究グループがいくつかあります。
The district treats it as our fan art system to attack these things
地区はこれをこれらのものを攻撃するためのファンアートシステムとして扱っています
Then try to make a therapeutic vaccine like this
それから、このような治療用ワクチンを作ってみてください
But the development doesn't seem to be so suitable
でも展開はあまり向いてないようです
So I would like to ask Professor Chang's opinion on the direction of such an attempt
そこで、そのような試みの方向性についてチャン教授の意見を聞きたいです。
Of course, that is just mentioned if, for example,
もちろん、それは、たとえば次のような場合に言及されただけです。
suppress this 16 or 17 performance
この16か17のパフォーマンスを抑制する
Then it's like nothing
それなら何もなかったかのように
So it could also be a form of therapy in reverse.
したがって、それは逆の治療法にもなり得るのです。
right
右
So I think this scientific research is that it can
この科学的研究は、
Like I just said Heeyum he had a dream
先ほど言ったように、ヒユムには夢がありました
have a clip up
クリップアップしてください
He just wanted to say it's okay
彼はただ大丈夫だと言いたかっただけです
then you do it
それならあなたがやります
you will know
あなたは知るだろう
Then
それから
and don't give up
そして諦めないでください
keep it up
がんばり続ける
Very likely
可能性が非常に高い
maybe you are the one
もしかしたらあなたがその人かもしれません
invent new treatments
新しい治療法を発明する
method person
方法論者
I think there is hope
希望はあると思う
ok because of time
時間の関係でわかりました
We thank Academician Zhang again
張学術院士に改めて感謝します
very good speech
とても良いスピーチ
Lyrics Li Zongsheng
歌詞李宗生